派拉蒙电影公司 出品
制片人：罗恩・迈克尔斯
领衔主演：莲莎・露夏恩
片名：贱女孩
这就是你的午餐，好吗？
This is your lunch, OK?
我还放了一美元钱在里面，你可以买些牛奶喝
Now, I put a dollar in there so you can buy some milk.
你可以问问大孩子在哪里买
You can ask one of the big kids where to do that.
记得住你的电话号码吗？ 我替你写了下来，就在这里面
You remember your phone number? I wrote it down for you, just in case.
放你口袋里，别搞丢了
Put it in your pocket, I don't want you to lose it.
好了？准备好了吗？
OK? You ready?
我想是的
I think so.
今天是凯蒂的大日子
It's Cady's big day.
作为父母，为孩子在校的第一天 而祈祷，我想这是很自然的事情
I guess it's natural for parents to cry on their kid's first day of school.
然而，这通常发生在孩子只有5岁的情况
But, you know, this usually happens when the kid is 5.
我16岁了，迄今为止，我还一直接受的家庭式教育
I'm 16 and until today, I was home-schooled.
我知道你会怎么想 “接受家庭式教育的孩子都是畸形”
I know what you're thinking. "Home-schooled kids are freaks. "
X-Y-L-O-C-A-R-P，硬木质果
X-Y-L-O-C-A-R-P. Xylocarp.
或者我们都信奉古怪的宗教，或其他什么的
Or that we're weirdly religious or something.
第三天，上帝创造了雷明顿推膛式步枪
And on the third day, God created the Remington bolt-action rifle
这样，人类就有可能战胜恐龙
so that Man could fight the dinosaurs.
以及同性恋
And the homosexuals.
- 阿门 - 阿门
- Amen. - Amen.
但我家却很普通
But my family's totally normal.
我父母都是动物学家
Except for the fact that both my parents are research zoologists
过去的12年，我们都是在非洲度过的
and we've spent the last 12 years in Africa.
除此之外，我的人生很精彩
I had a great life.
但之后我妈妈获得了西北大学的终身教授头衔
But then my mom got offered tenure at Northwestern University.
于是我就告别了非洲，踏入了高中的校门
So it was goodbye Africa and hello high school.
我没事儿，抱歉
I'm OK. Sorry.
我会注意安全的
I'll be careful.
主演：雷切尔・迈克亚当斯
主演：蒂姆・梅多斯
主演：艾米・波哈尔
主演：安娜・盖斯泰尔
主演：莱西・沙伯特
嗨
Hi.
不知道是否有人向你提及过我
I don't know if anyone told you about me.
我是新学员，我叫凯蒂・海伦
I'm a new student here. My name is Cady Heron.
再和我讲话，我就踢烂你的屁股
Talk to me again and I'll kick your ass.
主演：丽兹・卡普兰 丹尼尔・弗兰泽兹
你别想坐那儿，克里斯汀・哈德利的男友要坐那儿
You don't wanna sit there. Kristen Hadley's boyfriend is gonna sit there.
嘿，宝贝
Hey, baby.
主演：尼尔・弗林 乔纳森・本尼特 阿曼达・希耶福里德
他经常放屁的
He farts a lot.
主演：蒂娜・妃
嗨，大家好
Hey, everybody.
噢，上帝，非常抱歉
Oh, God, I'm so sorry.
不怪你，怪我倒霉
It's not you. I'm bad luck.
诺布利小姐？
Ms. Norbury?
我的T恤粘住我的汗衫了，是吗？
My T-shirt's stuck to my sweater, isn't it?
- 是的 - 太怪了
- Yeah. - Fantastic.
大家都还好吧？
Is everything all right in here?
- 噢，是的 - 那...
- Oh, yeah. - So...
- ...你暑假过得怎么样？ - 我离婚了
-...how was your summer? - I got divorced.
我的腕管症又复发了
My carpal tunnel came back.
- 我猜到了 - 是的，你该猜到了
- I win. - Yes, you do.
呃...我只是想告诉大家
Well, I just wanted to let everyone know
有位新同学加入了我们的集体
that we have a new student joining us.
她千里迢迢刚从非洲搬来这儿
She just moved here all the way from Africa.
欢迎啊
Welcome.
- 我来自密歇根 - 非常好
- I'm from Michigan. - Great.
她名叫堪蒂，堪蒂・海伦
Her name is Cady. Cady Heron.
- 是谁，堪蒂？ - 是我
- Where are you, Cady? - That's me.
- 应该念凯蒂 - 很抱歉
- It's pronounced like Katie. - My apologies.
我有个侄儿叫安福尼
I have a nephew named Anfernee,
当我叫他安东尼时，我知道他会发狂
and I know how mad he gets when I call him Anthony.
从未见过他那样生气，之后我才记起
Almost as mad as I get when I think about the fact
我姐姐实际上给他取名叫安福尼
that my sister named him Anfernee.
好了，我们欢迎凯蒂的到来
Well, welcome, Cady.
- 也感谢你，杜瓦尔先生 - 呃...多谢
- And thank you, Mr. Duvall. - Well, thank you.
另外...
And...
...要是你有何需要或者想找个人聊聊的话...
...if you need anything or if you wanna talk to somebody...
谢谢
Thanks.
另觅时间吧，我的上衣不透光的时候
Maybe some other time, when my shirt isn't see-through.
好吧
OK.
好，祝大家愉快
OK. Good day, everybody.
上学的第一天是个倒霉的日子
The first day of school was a blur.
令人压抑，荒诞怪异
A stressful, surreal blur.
大大小小的事儿，我都碰到了麻烦
I got in trouble for the most random things.
- 你去哪儿？ - 噢，我得去趟洗手间
- Where are you going? - Oh, I have to go to the bathroom.
你应该得到许可
You need the lavatory pass.
好吧，能去趟洗手间吗？
OK. Can I have the lavatory pass?
不错的尝试，先去坐下
Nice try. Have a seat.
我从未接触过这种生活，大人们都不信任我
I had never lived in a world where adults didn't trust me,
他们总对我吆喝
where they were always yelling at me.
- 别再往后读了！ - 不许用绿色的笔！
- Don't read ahead! - No green pen!
上课不许吃东西！
No food in class!
（外语）坐在你自己的位子上！
总监制：吉尔・梅希克
制片人：罗恩・迈克尔斯
我告诉过你，我全看到了
I told you, I saw the whole thing.
- 所有都看到了 - 乳头看到了吗？
- Everything. - Did you see nipple?
- 最关键是有没有看到乳头 - 真的，哥们
- It only counts if you saw a nipple. - That's true, dude.
我在非洲有很多朋友
I had a lot of friends in Africa.
什么？
What?
但是迄今为止，在伊云斯顿还一个也没有
But so far, none in Evanston.
导演：马克・沃特斯
嘿，第一天上学感觉如何？
Hey. How was your first day?
你头发本来就这个颜色？
Is that your natural hair color?
- 是的 - 太美了
- Yeah. - It's gorgeous.
谢谢
Thank you.
瞧，这就是我想要的颜色
See, this is the color I want.
他叫戴米恩，他一向行为夸张
This is Damian. He's almost too gay to function.
- 见到你很高兴 - 假发很漂亮啊，珍尼斯
- Nice to meet you. - Nice wig, Janis.
- 什么成分？ - 你妈的胸毛！
- What's it made of? - Your mom's chest hair!
- 我叫珍尼斯 - 你好，我叫凯蒂
- I'm Janis. - Hi, I'm Cady.
你们知道G14室在哪儿吗？
Do you guys know where Room G1 4 is?
“卫生保健，周二/周四，G14室”
"Health, Tuesday/Thursday, Room G1 4."
我想是在附楼上
I think that's in the back building.
- 是的，在附楼 - 是的，我们带你去
- Yeah, that's in the back building. - Yeah, we'll take you there.
谢谢
Thanks.
注意啦！新来的女生要过个路！
Watch out, please! New meat coming through!
“卫生保健，西班牙语”
"Health. Spanish."
你在念12年级的微积分？
You're taking 12th-grade calculus?
- 是的，我喜欢数学 - 为什么？
- Yeah, I like math. - Why?
因为它放之四海皆准
Because it's the same in every country.
妙极，这女孩很聪明
That's beautiful. This girl is deep.
附楼在哪儿？
Where's the back building?
1987年就化为平地了
It burned down in 1987.
是不是找起来稍微有些麻烦？
Won't we get in some sort of trouble for this?
我们干嘛要带给你麻烦呢？
Why would we get you into trouble?
我们是你朋友啊
We're your friends.
我知道敲课不对，但珍尼斯说我们是朋友
I know it's wrong to skip class, but Janis said we were friends.
我没道理拒绝朋友啊
And I was in no position to pass up friends.
我想我再也不记得卫生保健的第一堂课了
I guess I'll never know what I missed on that first day of health class.
不要发生性行为，因为会怀孕，死得很惨
Don't have sex. Because you will get pregnant and die.
不要采用传教士式体位（男上女下式）性交
Don't have sex in the missionary position,
也别采用站立式
don't have sex standing up.
就别去做，能保证吗？
Just don't do it, promise?
好了，每个人都来领些安全套
OK, everybody take some rubbers.
为什么他们不继续对你进行家庭式教育呢？
Why didn't they just keep home-schooling you?
他们想让我变得合群一些
They wanted me to get socialized.
噢，你会变得合群的，也罢，像你这样的女孩
Oh, you'll get socialized, all right. A little slice like you.
- 你们在说什么？ - 你是循规蹈矩的一类可爱女孩
- What are you talking about? - You're a regulation hottie.
- 什么？ - 保持住吧
- What? - Own it.
再给我说一次你名字的拼写，是凯蒂吗？
How do you spell your name again, Cady?
是凯蒂，C-A-D-Y
It's Cady. C-A-D-Y.
好的，我会叫你凯蒂的
Yeah, I'm gonna call you Cady.
名字中透露着圣洁，你看到 克伦・史密斯的运动服了吗？
In the name of all that is holy, will you look at Karen Smith's gym clothes?
当然，所有的“魔鬼身材”都在同一个体育班
Of course all The Plastics are in the same gym class.
- “魔鬼身材”是谁？ - 是青春皇室
- Who are The Plastics? - They're teen royalty.
把北岸高中比作《Us Weekly》杂志的话 她们便会一直出现在封面上
If North Shore was Us Weekly, they would always be on the cover.
那边那个人，就是克伦・史密斯
That one there, that's Karen Smith.
她是你会见到最笨的女孩之一
She is one of the dumbest girls you will ever meet.
戴米恩去年英语课和她邻桌
Damian sat next to her in English last year.
她问我“橘子”这个单词该怎么拼写
She asked me how to spell "orange".
那个年轻点的呢？是格雷琴・维纳斯
And that little one? That's Gretchen Wieners.
她绝对富有，因为她老爸发明了果馅卷
She's totally rich because her dad invented Toaster Strudel.
格雷琴・维纳斯知道所有人的私事
Gretchen Wieners knows everybody's business.
她知道所有人的一切
She knows everything about everyone.
这就是她头发特别多的原因，藏匿着秘密
That's why her hair is so big. It's full of secrets.
还有恶魔转世的莉贾娜・乔治
And evil takes a human form in Regina George.
别被欺骗了，因为她或许看起来 和常人一样，属于典型的自私、
Don't be fooled, because she may seem like your typical selfish, back-stabbing,
阴险、放荡的女孩，而事实上，她比这更胜一筹
slut-faced ho-bag. But in reality, she is so much more than that.
她是女王
She's the queen bee.
是明星，而其他两个仅仅是她的小奴才罢了
The star. Those other two are just her little workers.
莉贾娜・乔治
Regina George.
我又该怎么讲莉贾娜・乔治呢？
How do I even begin to explain Regina George?
莉贾娜・乔治是完美无瑕的
Regina George is flawless.
她有两个芬迪皮包，还有一辆凌志
She has two Fendi purses and a silver Lexus.
听说她的头发保险就达10000美元
I hear her hair's insured for $10,000.
听说她做汽车贸易，在日本
I hear she does car commercials. In Japan.
她最喜欢的电影是《校园蓝调》
Her favorite movie is Varsity Blues.
有一次，她在飞机上遇见了约翰・斯塔摩斯
One time, she met John Stamos on a plane.
他说她非常漂亮
And he told her she was pretty.
有一次，她用拳头打了我的脸
One time, she punched me in the face.
太绝了
It was awesome.
她看起来总是很凶，她总是能 赢得“春季狂欢节王后”的称号
She always looks fierce. She always wins Spring Fling Queen.
- 谁关心这个？ - 我关心
- Who cares? - I care.
每年高年级学生都会为低年级举行
Every year, the seniors throw this dance for the underclassmen
称为“春季狂欢节”的舞会
called The Spring Fling.
入选“春季狂欢节国王和王后”的人，无论是谁
And whomsoever is elected Spring Fling King and Queen
都会自然而然的成为学生会的头儿
automatically becomes head of the Student Activities Committee.
自从我成为学生会的积极分子以来
And since I am an active member of the Student Activities Committee,
我就会说，是的，我关心这个
I would say, yeah, I care.
戴米恩，你真是放浪形骸
Damian, you've truly out-gayed yourself.
给你，这是北岸中学的地图
Here. This map is gonna be your guide to North Shore.
你在自助餐厅里坐在哪儿是至关重要的
Now, where you sit in the cafeteria is crucial
因为你在那儿会遇到所有的人
because you got everybody there.
你会遇到和你一样的新生、后备军官训练队的家伙、
You got your freshmen, ROTC guys,
预科生、资浅代表队的小伙子们、
preps, JV jocks,
亚洲的蠢货们、
Asian nerds,
优秀的亚洲人、
cool Asians,
大学代表队的小伙子们、
varsity jocks,
充满敌意的黑妞儿、
unfriendly black hotties,
毫不克制暴食的女孩们、
girls who eat their feelings,
甘愿空腹的女孩们、
girls who don't eat anything,
不顾一切的赶超崇拜者、
desperate wannabes,
该死的人、
burnouts,
性敏感的家伙、
sexually active band geeks,
你见过的最优秀的人，
the greatest people you will ever meet
以及最烂的人，要提防“魔鬼身材”噢
and the worst. Beware of The Plastics.
嘿，我们在对新生做一个午餐时间调查
Hey. We're doing a lunchtime survey of new students.
可以回答几个问题吗？
Can you answer a few questions?
- 好吧 - 你的松糕涂黄油吗？
- OK. - Is your muffin buttered?
什么？
What?
需要我们安排人为你的松糕涂黄油吗？
Would you like us to assign someone to butter your muffin?
- 我的什么？ - 他让你心烦吗？
- My what? - Is he bothering you?
詹森，你怎么是这样一个烂货？
Jason, why are you such a skeez?
我只是友善而为
I'm just being friendly.
昨晚你应该给我电话的
You were supposed to call me last night.
詹森，三天后到我家来参加聚会 在我们面前，你就别和格雷琴在一起了
Jason. You do not come to a party at my house with Gretchen
去诱骗一个拙劣的无知女孩吧
and then scam on some poor, innocent girl right in front of us three days later.
她没兴趣了
She's not interested.
你想和他做爱吗？
Do you wanna have sex with him?
- 不，谢谢 - 很好，这样问题就解决了
- No, thank you. - Good. So it's settled.
你可以去修你的头发了
So you can go shave your back now.
拜，詹森
Bye, Jason.
婊子
Bitch.
别走啊，坐下来
Wait. Sit down.
说真的，坐下来吧
Seriously, sit down.
我怎么没见过你呢？
Why don't I know you?
我是新生，刚从非洲搬来这儿
I'm new. I just moved here from Africa.
- 什么？ - 我一直受家庭式教育
- What? - I used to be home-schooled.
且慢，什么？
Wait. What?
- 我妈妈在家里教我... - 不，不是
- My mom taught me at home... - No, no.
我知道什么是家庭式教育，我不是智障
I know what home-school is. I'm not retarded.
就是说事实上，之前你都没有去过真正的学校？
So you've actually never been to a real school before?
住嘴
Shut up.
- 我没有说话啊 - 受过家庭式教育
- I didn't say anything. - Home-schooled.
- 真有趣 - 谢谢
- That's really interesting. - Thanks.
而你长得似乎...真得很漂亮
But you're, like, really pretty.
- 谢谢 - 你也赞同
- Thank you. - So you agree.
- 什么？ - 你认为自己真得很漂亮
- What? - You think you're really pretty.
- 噢，我不得而知... - 噢，上帝，我喜欢你的手镯
- Oh, I don't know... - Oh, my God, I love your bracelet.
- 哪儿买的？ - 噢，我妈妈为我做的
- Where did you get it? - Oh, my mom made it for me.
- 很可爱啊 - 噢，如此诱惑
- It's adorable. - Oh, it's so fetch.
- 诱惑？ - 噢，这...好像是...俚语，来自英格兰
- What is "fetch"? - Oh, it's, like, slang. From England.
如果说你来自非洲...
So if you're from Africa...
...为什么你是白人呢？
...why are you white?
噢，上帝，卡伦，你不能只是问为什么是白人
Oh, my God, Karen, you can't just ask people why they're white.
我们能独处一会儿吗？
Could you give us some privacy for, like, one second?
好啊，当然可以
Yeah, sure.
你在干嘛？
What are you doing?
好了，你应该知道我们很少这样
OK, you should just know that we don't do this a lot,
所以可能...这是个...真正惊人的举措
so this is, like, a really huge deal.
我们想邀请你，这个礼拜
We wanna invite you to have lunch with us
每天都和我们共进午餐
every day for the rest of the week.
- 噢，好啊... - 绝好
- Oh, it's OK... - Coolness.
那我们明天再见
So we'll see you tomorrow.
周三我们会穿粉红色的衣服
On Wednesdays, we wear pink.
噢，上帝！好了，你一定得那样，好吗？
Oh, my God! OK, you have to do it, OK?
然后你得告诉我，莉贾娜说的所有恐怖的事情
And then you have to tell me all the horrible things that Regina says.
莉贾娜看上去蛮可爱的
Regina seems sweet.
莉贾娜・乔治并不可爱
Regina George is not sweet.
她是淫荡的街妓！她毁了我的一生！
She's a scum-sucking road whore! She ruined my life!
她很不可思议，但也很可怕
She's fabulous, but she's evil.
- 嗨，出去！ - 噢，上帝，丹尼・德・维托
- Hey, get out of here! - Oh, my God, Danny DeVito.
我想做你的工作！
I love your work!
- 你为什么恨她？ - 你说谁？
- Why do you hate her? - What do you mean?
莉贾娜，你看上去对她恨之入骨
Regina. You seem to really hate her.
不错，你想问什么？
Yes. What's your question?
- 呃...我想问，为什么呢？ - 莉贾娜制造谣言...
- Well, my question is, why? - Regina started this rumor
- 说珍尼丝... - 戴米恩！我们没有好吗？
- that Janis was... - Damian! Shall we not?
看看，这不是恨她，好吗？
Now, look. This isn't about hating her, OK?
我只是想，如果你和她们在一起
I just think that it would be, like, a fun little experiment
然后告诉我们她们谈论的一切 这...或许...是个有趣的小试验
if you were to hang out with them and then tell us everything that they say.
- 我们能谈论什么呢？ - 头发产品
- What do we even talk about? - Hair products.
- 艾什顿・库奇 - 是乐队吗？
- Ashton Kutcher. - Is that a band?
就这样好吗？拜托了？
Would you just do it? Please?
好，没问题，你们有没有什么粉红色的东西？
OK, fine. Do you have anything pink?
- 有啊 - 没有
- Yes. - No.
第八个学时，我很开心能来到数学课堂上
By eighth period, I was so happy to get to math class.
我是说，我很擅长数学，我能领悟数学的奥妙
I mean, I'm good at math. I understand math.
数学课上，没有什么能难倒我
Nothing in math class could mess me up.
嘿，有铅笔吗借我？
Hey, do you have a pencil I can borrow?
一生中，我另外只爱过一次
I've only had one other crush in my life.
他叫恩弗米，我们都只有5岁
His name was Nfume, and we were 5.
我喜欢你
走开！
没有成功
It didn't work out.
但这次却像一辆巨大的 黄色校车一样撞上了我
But this one hit me like a big, yellow school bus.
- 凯蒂，你说什么？ - 他...
- Cady, what do you say? - He was...
如此可爱
So cute.
我是说，A(N)等于N加1除以4
I mean, A-sub-N equals N plus one over four.
对了
That's right.
很好，很好
That's good. Very good.
好了，下面我们来布置作业
All right, let's talk about your homework.
嘿，你第二天过的怎么样？
Hey. How was your second day?
- 很好 - 人们都还友善吧？
- Fine. - Were people nice?
- 不 - 你交朋友了吗？
- No. - Did you make any friends?
有啊
Yeah.
和“魔鬼身材”共进午餐就像离开了现实世界
Having lunch with The Plastics was like leaving the actual world
...而进入了“女孩世界”一样
and entering "Girl World".
而“女孩世界”又有很多规则
And Girl World had a lot of rules.
你不能在连续的两天内穿同一件背心
You can't wear a tank top two days in a row,
你一个礼拜只能疏一次马尾辫
and you can only wear your hair in a ponytail once a week.
我想今天你已经做好了选择
So I guess you picked today.
噢，我们只在礼拜五穿牛仔裤或者运动裤
Oh, and we only wear jeans or track pants on Fridays.
如果你违反任何规则，你都不能和我们共进午餐了
Now, if you break any of these rules, you can't sit with us at lunch.
我的意思是不仅仅是你，我们任何人都一样
I mean, not just you. Like, any of us.
好了，譬如我今天穿牛仔裤
OK, like, if I was wearing jeans today,
我就要坐在那边，和那些易容疯子呆在一起
I would be sitting over there with the art freaks.
噢，我们叫人同我们共进午餐前，通常会投票
Oh, and we always vote before we ask someone to eat lunch with us
因为你得考虑群里的其他人
because you have to be considerate of the rest of the group.
呃...我是说...如果没有朋友们 的同意，即使穿上去很好看...
Well, I mean, you wouldn't buy a skirt without asking your friends first
- 你也不能买任何衣服 - 这也不能？
- if it looks good on you. - I wouldn't?
是的，噢，对男孩也一样
Right. Oh, and it's the same with guys.
譬如，你或许觉得你喜欢某人 但你不能犯错误
Like, you may think you like someone, but you could be wrong.
120卡热量就有48卡来自脂肪，多大比例？
A hundred and twenty calories and 48 calories from fat. What percent is that?
48比120？
Forty-eight into 120?
我只能吃脂肪热量低于30%的食物
I'm only eating foods with less than 30 percent calories from fat.
是40%
It's 40 percent.
呃，48比120等于X比100
Well, 48 over 120 equals X over 100,
然后用十字相乘法得出X的值
and then you cross-multiply and get the value of X.
随便了，我去拿奶酪薯条
Whatever. I'm getting cheese fries.
你有见到还觉得不错的男孩吗？
So have you seen any guys that you think are cute yet?
呃，我上微积分课的时候有个男生...
Well, there's this guy in my calculus class...
- 谁？ - 高年级的？
- Who is it? - It's a senior?
- 叫亚伦・塞缪尔 - 不！
- His name's Aaron Samuels. - No!
噢，不，你不能喜欢上亚伦・塞缪尔
Oh, no, you can't like Aaron Samuels.
他是莉贾娜的前男友
That's Regina's ex-boyfriend.
他们一年前才分手
They went out for a year.
不错，去年夏天他甩掉她时
Yeah, and then she was devastated
她都快崩溃了
when he broke up with her last summer.
我感觉是她为了谢恩・阿曼而一脚蹬了他
I thought she dumped him for Shane Oman.
好了，不管怎样，朋友的前男友是不能够追的
OK, irregardless. Ex-boyfriends are just off-limits to friends.
我的意思是，这就...好像是...女权运动的规则
I mean, that's just, like, the rules of feminism.
别担心，你说的我不会告诉莉贾娜的
Don't worry. I'll never tell Regina what you said.
这是我们之间的小秘密
It'll be our little secret.
我们把无穷几何级数的和定义为...
We define the sum of the infinite geometric series...
尽管我不能够喜欢亚伦
Even though I wasn't allowed to like Aaron,
但我还是可以看他
I was still allowed to look at him.
想他
And think about him.
和他说话
And talk to him.
- 嗨，亚... - 嗨，你是来自非洲的女孩，对吗？
- Hey, Aar... - Hey, you're the Africa girl, right?
- 是的 - 我是凯文・纳泊尔
- Yeah. - I'm Kevin Gnapoor,
北岸中学数学奥赛队的队长
captain of the North Shore Mathletes.
我们参加数学竞赛，挑战州内其他高中
We participate in math challenges against other high schools in the state,
如果我们能吸收一位女生，就会得到双倍的奖金
and we can get twice as much funding if we've got a girl.
所以你应该考虑是否加入
So you should think about joining.
- 噢，你加入真是太好了 - 是的，的确是
- Oh, you'd be perfect for it. - Yeah, definitely.
极好，极好，我给你我的名片
Great, great. Let me give you my card.
好了，好好考虑一下吧
OK, so think it over.
因为我们要定购统一的服装了
Because we'd like to get jackets.
好吧
OK.
嗨！
Hey!
上车，衰人，我们去购物
Get in, loser. We're going shopping.
莉贾娜就像我以前的芭比娃娃
Regina's like the Barbie doll I never had.
我从未见人如此富有魅力
I'd never seen anybody so glamorous.
- 你觉得北岸高中怎么样？ - 很好啊
- So how do you like North Shore? - It's good.
我想加入数学奥赛队
I think I'm joining the Mathletes.
- 不！不，不 - 不，不
- No! No, no. - No, no.
你不能加入，那是自杀
You cannot do that. That is social suicide.
该死，我们来引导你，你能荣幸
Damn, you are so lucky you have us to guide you.
走在老果园广场，我似乎回想起在非洲的情形
Being at Old Orchard Mall kind of reminded me of being home in Africa.
在水潭旁边，动物都处于热浪之中
By the watering hole. When the animals are in heat.
噢，上帝，那是詹森！
Oh, my God, there's Jason!
哪儿？噢，他在那儿
Where? Oh, there he is.
- 他和泰勒・威德尔在一起 - 听说他们吹了
- And he's with Taylor Wedell. - I heard they're going out.
等等，詹森是不会和泰勒吹的
Wait. Jason's not going out with Taylor.
不，他不能那样扔下你不管
No. He cannot blow you off like that.
他这样一个烂人，给我你的电话
He's such a little skeez. Give me your phone.
- 你不是想给他打电话吧？ - 你觉得我是白痴吗？
- You're not gonna call him, right? - Do you think I'm an idiot?
没有
No.
- 接南林荫道的威德尔 - 会要求主叫者身份的
- Wedell on South Boulevard. - Caller lD.
如果你联接的是信息中心就不会
Not when you connect from lnformation.
- 喂？ - 喂
- Hello? - Hello.
麻烦让泰勒・威德尔接电话？
May I please speak to Taylor Wedell?
他不在家，你哪位？
She's not home yet. Who's calling?
噢，我是计划生育委员会的苏珊
Oh, this is Susan from Planned Parenthood.
我得到了她的检测结果，你 是否能让她尽快给我回电话
I have her test results. If you can have her give me a call as soon as she can.
情况紧急，谢谢
It's urgent. Thank you.
她再也不会和任何人出来了
She's not going out with anyone.
好，真是诱惑
OK, that was so fetch.
妈妈
Mom.
你家真爽
Your house is really nice.
我知道，对吧？
I know, right?
保证你会看到她妈的乳房工程
Make sure you check out her mom's boob job.
像岩石一样坚固
They're hard as rocks.
我回来啦！嗨，凯莉
I'm home! Hey, Kylie.
嗨
Hey.
嗨，嗨，嗨！我最好的女友怎么样啦？
Hey, hey, hey! How are my best girlfriends?
嗨，乔治夫人，这是凯蒂
Hey, Mrs. George. This is Cady.
你好，甜心
Hello, sweetheart.
- 嗨 - 欢迎来玩
- Hi. - Welcome to our home.
只想告诉你，有任何需要，都别客气，好吗？
Just want you to know, if you need anything, don't be shy, OK?
这个家里没什么规则，我不像一个循规蹈矩的母亲
There are no rules in this house. I'm not like a regular mom.
我是一个很酷的母亲，对吧，莉贾娜？
I'm a cool mom. Right, Regina?
- 别说了 - 好吧
- Please stop talking. - OK.
我要用“曲线节”来款待你们
I'm gonna make you girls a "hump day" treat.
这是你的房间？
This is your room?
是我父母的房间，但我要他们换给我
It was my parents' room, but I made them trade me.
嘿，调到98.8赫兹
Hey, put on 98.8.
凯蒂，你知道这是谁唱的吗？
Cady, do you even know who sings this?
- “辣妹组合”？ - 我喜欢她
- The Spice Girls? - I love her.
她就像个火星人
She's like a Martian.
- 上帝，我的臀部奇大无比！ - 噢，拜托，我讨厌我的小腿
- God, my hips are huge! - Oh, please. I hate my calves.
至少你们可以穿吊带衫，我肩膀和男人一样宽
At least you guys can wear halters. I've got man shoulders.
过去，我觉得只有脂肪和皮肤会不妥
I used to think there was just fat and skinny.
显然，身上很多地方都会不妥
Apparently, there's a lot of things that can be wrong on your body.
- 我的发根太奇怪了 - 我的毛孔粗大
- My hairline is so weird. - My pores are huge.
我的甲床太烂了
My nail beds suck.
清晨，我呼吸着实糟糕
I have really bad breath in the morning.
嗨，姑娘们，4点到6点是幸福的时光！
Hey, you guys. Happy hour is from 4 to 6!
谢谢
Thanks.
这含酒精吗？
Is there alcohol in this?
噢，上帝，甜心，你把我想成哪种母亲了？
Oh, God, honey, no. What kind of mother do you think I am?
你想要点？要是你想，我愿意让你在屋里喝点
Do you want a bit? If you're gonna drink, I'd rather you do it in the house.
- 不，谢谢 - 好吧
- No, thank you. - OK.
姑娘们，411是什么？
So, you guys, what is the 41 1?
大家都是在做什么？
What has everybody been up to?
热衷的话题是什么？都告诉我吧
What is the hot gossip? Tell me everything.
你们听到些什么？最酷的睡衣？
What are you guys listening to? What's the cool jams?
妈妈
Mom.
- 你去搞搞头发吧？ - 好吧
- Could you go fix your hair? - OK.
你们这些姑娘让我焕发春光，噢，我如此爱你们
You girls keep me young. Oh, I love you so much.
噢，上帝，我记得这个
Oh, my God, I remember this.
- 我永远都不会看那个 - 来瞧瞧，凯蒂
- I haven't looked at that in forever. - Come check it out, Cady.
这是我们的“烈火红唇之书”
It's our Burn Book.
瞧，我们从年刊上剪下靓女图案
See, we cut out girls' pictures from the yearbook,
然后我们加以评述
and then we wrote comments.
- “Trang Pak是个格罗斯基的小贱人” - 仍然成立
- "Trang Pak is a grotsky little byotch." - Still true.
- “道恩・施韦策是个肥胖的处女” - 只有一半对
- "Dawn Schweitzer is a fat virgin." - Still half true.
“安柏・德・阿莱希奥”她与“热狗”有染
"Amber D'Alessio." She made out with a hot dog.
“珍尼斯・伊安，同性恋者”
"Janis lan, dyke."
- 那是谁？ - 我想是那个叫戴米恩的孩子
- Who is that? - I think that's that kid Damian.
是的，他老是行为夸张
Yeah. He's almost too gay to function.
有趣，把那东西放下
That's funny. Put that in there.
噢，不，或许珍尼斯只会对此说好
Oh, no. Maybe that was only OK when Janis said it.
那本“烈火红唇之书”，记载的都是
And they have this Burn Book where they write mean things
- 我们这级女孩们的低贱传闻 - 她们怎么说我的？
- about all the girls in our grade. - What does it say about me?
- 里面没有你 - 那群婊子
- You're not in it. - Those bitches.
- 这能缩小我的毛孔吗？ - 不，凯蒂
- Will this minimize my pores? - No. Cady,
你去把那本书偷来
you gotta steal that book.
- 不行！ - 噢，拜托，我们可以公开
- No way! - Oh, come on. We could publish it,
这样大家都会看见她的本来面目
and then everybody would see what an ax-wound she really is.
- 我不会去偷的 - 你完全能办得到
- I don't steal. - That is for your feet.
凯蒂，可恶的人有两种
Cady, there are two kinds of evil people.
十恶不赦的一种
People who do evil stuff,
还有就是目睹邪恶而袖手旁观者
and people who see evil stuff being done and don't try to stop it.
你是说我应该去烧掉那女人的衣服？
Does that mean I'm morally obligated to burn that lady's outfit?
噢，上帝，那是诺贝利小姐
Oh, my God, that's Ms. Norbury.
我喜欢在学校外见到老师
I love seeing teachers outside of school.
就像看到小狗用后腿走路一样
It's like seeing a dog walk on its hind legs.
嗨，大家好，怎么？我还不知你们在这儿上班呢
Hey, guys, what's up? I didn't know you worked here.
是的，我负责中等价位的肥皂
Yeah, moderately priced soaps are my calling.
- 你购物吗？ - 不，我只是和我男友路过此处
- You shopping? - No, I'm just here with my boyfriend.
开玩笑的，有时年龄大的人也会开玩笑
Joking. Sometimes older people make jokes.
我祖母喝醉了就会把假发摘掉
My nana takes her wig off when she's drunk.
你祖母和我有共同之处
Your nana and I have that in common.
不，事实上，我来这儿是因为一周有几个晚上
No, actually, I'm just here because I bartend a couple nights a week
我要去PJ・卡莱米提酒吧点当服务员
down at P.J. Calamity's.
凯蒂，我希望你加入数学奥赛队，知道吗
Cady, I hope you do join Mathletes, you know,
因为我们也是几个礼拜前才开始的
because we start in a couple weeks
我想吸收一个女生加入
and I would love to have a girl on the team,
知道吗，这样队里就有女孩了
just, you know, so the team could meet a girl.
- 我想我会加入的 - 太好了
- I think I'm gonna do it. - Great.
你不能去数奥小组，那是集体自杀
You can't join Mathletes. It's social suicide.
谢谢，戴米恩
Thanks, Damian.
呃...场面已经足够尴尬了
Well, this has been sufficiently awkward.
我们明天再见面吧
And I'll see you guys tomorrow.
- 拜 - 拜
- Bye. - Bye.
噢，老兄，没前途了
Oh, man, that is bleak.
你什么时候才能再见到莉贾娜？
So when are you gonna see Regina again?
我不会再监视她的，感觉很怪
I can't spy on her anymore. It's weird.
拜托，她不会察觉的，这是我们俩的小秘密
Come on, she's never gonna find out. It'll be like our little secret.
- 喂？ - 我知道你的秘密了
- Hello? - I know your secret.
噢，上帝，穿帮了吧
Oh, God, busted.
忏悔吧，哭吧，不，镇定下来
Just start apologizing and crying. No, play it cool.
秘密？你在说什么啊？
Secret? What are you saying about?
格雷琴告诉我，说你喜欢亚伦・塞缪尔
Gretchen told me that you like Aaron Samuels.
我是说，我并不在意，想怎么就怎么吧
I mean, I don't care, do whatever you want.
但我要告诉你有关亚伦的事：
But let me just tell you something about Aaron:
他关心的只有学校、他的妈妈还有他的哥们
All he cares about is school and his mom and his friends.
- 这不好吗？ - 但如果你喜欢他...
- Is that bad? - But if you like him...
不论如何，我是说，如果你 愿意的话，我会向他提及你
Whatever. I mean, I could talk to him for you if you want.
真的？你会提到我？我是说，也不会尴尬，对吗？
Really? You would do that? I mean, nothing embarrassing, though, right?
噢，不，相信我，我完全明白应该怎么做
Oh, no, trust me. I know exactly how to play it.
不过等等，格雷琴告诉了我 一切，你不会生她的气吧？
But wait. Aren't you so mad at Gretchen for telling me?
- 不会的 - 因为如果你会生气
- No. - Because if you are,
你可以给我讲，她这样做的确不够朋友
you can tell me. It was a really bitchy thing for her to do.
是啊，相当不够朋友，但我不会生气的
Yeah, it was pretty bitchy, but I'm not mad.
我是说，我想她只是比较关心这事儿
I mean, I guess she just likes the attention.
听到了吗，格雷琴？我都说了，她不会生你气的
See, Gretch? I told you she's not mad at you.
我无法相信你只是觉得我比较关注！
I can't believe you think I like attention!
好，爱你们，明天见
OK, love you. See you tomorrow.
第一轮三方通话攻击，我算挺过来了
I had survived my first three-way calling attack.
感谢莉贾娜的祝福，我开始越来越多接触亚伦了
And with Regina's blessing, I started talking to Aaron more and more.
十月三号，他向我打听日期
On October 3rd, he asked me what day it was.
十月三号
It's October 3rd.
两周后，我们又说话了
Two weeks later, we spoke again.
下雨了
It's raining.
是的
Yeah.
但是我还想进展更快些
But I wanted things to move faster.
于是我纵容着自己
So I followed my instincts.
嘿，我完全听不懂，你能帮我吗？
Hey, I'm totally lost. Can you help me?
- 但是我能听懂 - 是的
- But I wasn't lost. - Yeah.
我完全明白诺贝利小姐在说什么
I knew exactly what Ms. Norbury was talking about.
这是因数，所以你用N乘以每一个数
It's a factorial, so you multiply each one by N.
错了
Wrong.
是求和吗？
Is that the summation?
是的，一回事儿
Yeah, they're the same thing.
错了，他错得如此厉害
Wrong. He was so wrong.
谢谢，我...我现在明白了
Thanks. I... I get it now.
请开灯，好，明天见
Lights, please. OK. See you guys tomorrow.
今晚我朋友克里斯家要举行万圣节聚会
We're having a Halloween party at my friend Chris' tonight.
想来吗？
You wanna come?
好啊，当然
Yeah, sure.
太好了，这是地址
Great. Here's where it is.
是个化妆晚会，人们都会穿得很可爱
It's a costume party. People get pretty into it.
好的
OK.
梯子只能一人上去
That flier admits one person only,
所以别带另外的男孩一起
so don't bring some other guy with you.
“酷棒”
"Grool."
我是想说“酷毕”，而我又已经在说“棒极”
I meant to say "cool" and then I started to say "great".
不错，呃...酷棒
Right. Well...grool.
晚上见
See you tonight.
嗨，非洲人，你留下来，数奥队要开会
Hey, Africa. You staying for the Mathletes meeting?
好的，我就回来
Yeah, I'll be right back.
好了，我撒谎了，但我必须得回家化妆
OK, I lied. But I had to go home and work on my costume.
在常规的世界里，万圣节时，孩子们会盛妆出场
In the regular world, Halloween is when children dress up in costumes
索要糖果
and beg for candy.
在“女孩世界”里，万圣节却是一个晚上
In Girl World, Halloween is the one night a year
女孩们都穿得像个荡妇
when a girl can dress like a total slut
却绝不允许其他人对此稍作评论
and no other girls can say anything about it.
赤身裸体的女孩们只穿上紧身胸衣
The hard-core girls just wear lingerie
戴上各种动物的耳朵
and some form of animal ears.
他看起来是不是很棒，甜心？
Doesn't she look great, honey?
- 你扮的什么？ - 老鼠
- What are you? - I'm a mouse.
很不幸，打扮放荡这个规则没人告诉过我
Unfortunately, no one told me about the slut rule.
于是我便以这种形象露面了
So I showed up like this.
嗨
Hey.
对！对！
Yes! Yes!
嗨
Hey.
你怎么这么吓人？
Why are you dressed so scary?
万圣节啊
It's Halloween.
看到詹森了吗？
Have you seen Jason?
知道今晚谁的装束好吗？
You know who's looking fine tonight?
塞斯・莫萨克斯基
Seth Mosakowski.
- 好了，你不能只是说啊 - 什么？他通晓接吻技巧
- OK, you did not just say that. - What? He's a good kisser.
他是你堂兄啊
He's your cousin.
是的，也是我第一个堂兄
Yeah, but he's my first cousin.
- 不错 - 你会有堂兄、
- Right. - So you have your cousins
有第一个堂兄
and then you have your first cousins,
- 接着还会有第二个堂兄... - 不，甜心
- then you have your second cousins... - No, honey.
并非如此，对吧？
That's not right, is it?
并非如此
That is so not right.
- 嗨！ - 嗨
- Hey! - Hey.
你来啦
You made it.
你像个...僵尸新娘
And you are...a zombie bride.
是“前妻”
An "ex-wife".
不错，想喝点什么吗？
Love it. Can I get you something to drink?
- 好的 - 马上回来
- Yeah. - Be right back.
- 谢谢 - 马上回来
Thanks.
克伦，别动
Karen, stop it.
- 别，克伦... - 嗨，塞斯！
- Don't, Karen... - Hey, Seth!
嗨
Hey.
噢，不
Oh, no.
有人告诉过你吗？
Didn't anybody tell you?
你就应该穿成这样
You were supposed to wear a costume.
闭嘴，我要和你谈谈
Shut up. I need to talk to you.
- 认识那个叫凯蒂的女孩吗？ - 认识，她很棒
- You know that girl Cady? - Yeah, she's cool.
今晚是我邀请她来的
I invited her tonight.
呃，小心点，因为她已深深的迷恋上你
Well, be careful because she has a huge crush on you.
真的？你怎么知道？
Really? How do you know?
她告诉我的
Because she told me.
她告诉了所有人，实际上，她蛮可爱的
She tells everybody. It's kind of cute, actually.
她就像个小姑娘，她爱把东西都写下来
She's like a little girl. She, like, writes all over her notebook,
“亚伦・塞缪尔夫人”
"Mrs. Aaron Samuels."
还有她把一件T恤上写上“我迷恋亚伦”
And she made this T-shirt that says "l heart Aaron"
然后穿在所有的衣服里面
and she wears it under all her clothes.
- 噢，拜托 - 呃...这也难怪她？
- Oh, come on. - Well, who can blame her?
我是说，你这么帅气
I mean, you're gorgeous.
好，听着，我并非想说她在追求你
And OK, look, I'm not saying she's a stalker,
他收集你用过的克里雷克斯面巾纸
but she saved this Kleenex you used
还说要用来召唤非洲巫术
and she said she's gonna do some kind of African voodoo with it
让你喜欢她
to make you like her.
什么？
What?
就像这样
This was it.
莉贾娜说她要和亚伦谈谈我，现在就正在谈
Regina said she would talk to Aaron for me, and now she was.
我知道她在社交方面愚蠢 而怪异，但她是我的朋友
I know she's kind of socially retarded and weird, but she's my friend,
所以你向我保证，别去取笑她
so just promise me you won't make fun of her.
我当然不会取笑她
Of course I'm not gonna make fun of her.
为什么珍尼斯会恨莉贾娜呢？
How could Janis hate Regina?
她是个如此可爱的...
She was such a good...
荡妇！
Slut!
你干什么啊？你和我都分手了
What are you doing? You broke up with me.
疯了，我为什么要和你分手？
That's crazy. Why would I break up with you?
你如此有魅力
You're so hot.
这个面具很恐怖，兄弟
That's a scary mask, bro.
我从未有过这种感觉
I had never felt this feeling before.
居然能听到自己的心跳
I could hear my heartbeat in my ears.
我的胃就像要吐出来一样
My stomach felt like it was going to fall out my butt.
喉咙里这团东西，就像硬吞了一粒大药丸
I had this lump in my throat like after you dry-swallow a big pill.
我恨莉贾娜，我恨她！
I hated Regina. I hated her!
她又夺走了他
She took him back.
莉贾娜把亚伦夺了过去
Regina took Aaron back.
- 噢，不，凯蒂 - 她为什么要这样？
- Oh, no, Cady. - Why would she do that?
因为她是生活的毁灭者
Because she's a life-ruiner.
她毁了别人的一生
She ruins people's lives.
我们13岁时，她就让人们在请愿书上签名
When we were 1 3, she made people sign this petition
- 说什么珍尼斯... - 戴米恩！拜托！
- saying that Janis was... - Damian! Please!
听着，她再也别想得逞了，对吧？
Look, she's not gonna get away with this again, OK?
- 我们得采取措施 - 我们？
- We're gonna do something. - We are?
莉贾娜・乔治是个邪恶的独裁者
Regina George is an evil dictator.
那怎么才能推翻这个独裁者呢？
Now, how do you overthrow a dictator?
就要切断她的资源
You cut off her resources.
没有这些，莉贾娜将一无是处 那就是她挚爱的男人...
Regina would be nothing without her high-status man candy...
（亚伦・塞缪尔）
...技术上讲，确有绝好的身段...
...technically good physique...
（“热辣”躯体）
...以及一群愚蠢的忠诚的追随者
...and ignorant band of loyal followers.
（贱人死党）
凯蒂，要是你愿意按我说的做
Now, Cady, if we want this to work,
你就得继续粘住她们，显出若无其事的样子
you are gonna have to keep hanging out with them like nothing is wrong.
可以吗？
Can you do it?
可以
I can do it.
好的，我们来搞这个臭婊子
OK, let's rock this bitch.
装作若无其事，显出不可思议的放松
Pretending like nothing was wrong turned out to be surprisingly easy.
莉贾娜要我告诉你，她想让你继续试图粘住亚伦
Regina wanted me to tell you that she was trying to hook you up with Aaron,
但是他只想和她和好
but he was just interested in getting her back.
这不是莉贾娜的过错啊
And that's not Regina's fault.
- 对，我知道 - 好，就是说你不会生莉贾娜的气？
- No, I know. - OK, so you're not mad at Regina?
- 上帝，不 - 噢，好的，很好
- God, no. - Oh, OK, good.
因为莉贾娜要我给你讲讲这个
Because Regina wanted me to give you this.
这是南岸果肉系列
It's called the South Beach Fat Flush,
都是72小时内轧出的越橘汁
and all you drink is cranberry juice for 72 hours.
这并非纯越橘汁
This isn't even cranberry juice.
这是越橘汁饮料，都是糖分
It's cranberry juice cocktail. It's all sugar.
- 我想减掉3磅的体重 - 你疯了
- I wanna lose 3 pounds. - You're crazy.
你干嘛把头发弄成这样？往后疏看上去很性感啊
Why do you wear your hair like that? You hair looks so sexy pushed back.
凯蒂，你觉得她的头发往后疏是不是很性感
Cady, will you please tell him his hair looks sexy pushed back.
莉贾娜故意当着我的面，对亚伦卖弄骚姿
Regina was dangling Aaron in front of me on purpose.
我知道在动物世界里，这种情况如何处理
I knew how this would be settled in the animal world.
但这是“女孩世界”
But this was Girl World.
你把头发往后疏会很性感
Your hair looks sexy pushed back.
在“女孩世界”，所有较量都在暗中进行
And in Girl World, all the fighting had to be sneaky.
我喝了所有的越橘汁都会长痘痘
All this cranberry juice is making me break out.
等等，我带一个非常有效的护肤品给你
Wait. I have this really good skin stuff I'll bring you.
好的
OK.
我们睁大了眼睛，寻找报复的机会
We kept our eyes open for opportunities for sabotage.
莉贾娜
Regina.
- 给你 - 谢谢
- Here you go. - Thank you.
- 嗨 - 嗨
- Hey. - Hey.
你的脸上像有一股薄荷油味
Your face smells like peppermint.
你们可真是大傻瓜
This is ass, you guys.
一个月了，我们所做的就是 让莉贾娜的脸，闻起来像脚掌的味道
It's been a month, and all we've done is make Regina's face smell like a foot.
我在唱诗班真得很忙
I've been really busy with choir.
我们必须击破格雷琴・维纳斯
We gotta crack Gretchen Wieners.
击破格雷琴后，我们再去击破
We crack Gretchen, and then we crack the lock
莉贾娜所有的不耻行径
on Regina's whole dirty history.
- 再说一次“击破”呢 - 击破
- Say "crack" again. - Crack.
- 好了，我们晚上在碰面吧 - 我不能来
- All right, let's reconvene tonight. - I can't.
我得去莉贾娜家，为演唱会做排练
I have to go to Regina's to practice for the talent show.
- 我们要为一首歌配舞... - 《圣诞铃声响》
- We're doing a dance to this song... - "Jingle Bell Rock."
你们知道这支歌？
You guys know that song?
英语母语国家的人都知道这支歌
Everybody in the English-speaking world knows that song.
每年都要唱
They do it every year.
呃，我要去学会
Well, I have to learn it.
快走
Go.
- 嗨 - 你怎么在和珍尼斯・伊安说话？
- Hey. - Why were you talking to Janis lan?
我不知道啊，我是说，她很奇怪
I don't know, I mean, she's so weird.
她走上来就开始和我说什么“击破”之类的话
She just, you know, came up to me and started talking to me about crack.
她真悲惨
She's so pathetic.
我给你讲讲珍尼斯・伊安的事吧
Let me tell you something about Janis lan.
我们中学时是最好的朋友
We were best friends in middle school.
我知道的，对吧？
I know, right?
很尴尬，我甚至不...不论什么
It's so embarrassing. I don't even... Whatever.
之后八年级时，我开始和第一任男友出去
So then in eighth grade, I started going out with my first boyfriend,
凯尔，她绝对帅气，但之后他去了印第安纳
Kyle, who was totally gorgeous, but then he moved to lndiana.
而珍尼斯呢，很奇怪，好像在妒嫉他
And Janis was, like, weirdly jealous of him.
如果我不理他而和凯尔呆在一起
Like, if I would blow her off to hang out with Kyle,
她可能会说“你为什么不给我回电呢？”
she'd be like, "Why didn't you call me back?"
然后我就会说“你为什么老烦我呢？”
And I'd be like, "Why are you so obsessed with me?"
之后，在我的生日晚会上，所有人都在场
So then, for my birthday party, which was an all-girls pool party,
我说“珍尼斯，我不能邀请你 因为我觉得你是同性恋...”
I was like, "Janis, I can't invite you, because I think you're a lesbian."
我的意思是，我不能让同性恋来我的晚会吧
I mean, I couldn't have a lesbian at my party.
女孩们会穿泳装的啊
There are gonna be girls there in their bathing suits.
我是说，对吧？她是个同性恋
I mean, right? She was a lesbian.
后来他妈妈打电话给我妈，开始对她大呼小叫
So then her mom called my mom and started yelling at her.
真是脑袋有问题
It was so retarded.
然后他就辍学了，因为没人愿意和她讲话
And then she dropped out of school because no one would talk to her.
秋天她回到高中的时候
When she came back in the fall for high school,
她剪掉了所有的头发，完全变了
all of her hair was cut off and she was totally weird,
现在我怀疑她在吸食可卡因
and now I guess she's on crack.
噢，上帝！我喜欢你这件衣服
Oh, my God! I love your skirt.
在哪儿买的？
Where did you get it?
这是我妈妈80年代的衣服
It was my mom's in the '80s.
古董啊，让人崇敬
Vintage. So adorable.
谢谢
Thanks.
这是我见过的最丑的衣服
That is the ugliest F-ing skirt I've ever seen.
噢，上帝，我喜欢你的手镯，哪儿买的？
Oh, my God, I love your bracelet. Where did you get it?
你想送她们糖果棒吗？
So are you gonna send any candy canes?
不，我不想送，我只想收到
No. I don't send them, I just get them.
你最好送我一个，小贱人
So you better send me one, byotch.
爱你
Love you.
我最多只送她一个
I was definitely sending her one.
我要用三个糖果棒来击破格雷琴・维纳斯
I was gonna use three candy canes to crack Gretchen Wieners.
三个，谢谢
Three, please.
“为什么他要像巨人一样跨骑在狭窄的世界上？”
"Why, Man, he doth bestride the narrow world like a colossus"
可以说成是
might translate into
“为什么他如此巨大而有令人讨厌呢？”
"Why is he so huge and obnoxious?"
- 糖果棒来啦！ - 好啦，赶快
- Candy cane-grams! - OK, hurry up.
泰勒・齐墨曼？两个给你的
Taylor Zimmerman? Two for you.
格伦・库科？
Glenn Cocco?
四个你的，格伦・库科，拿去，格伦・库科
Four for you, Glenn Cocco. You go, Glenn Cocco.
然后是凯蒂・海伦
And Cady Heron.
有叫凯蒂・海伦的吗？
Do we have a Cady Heron here?
- 我是 - 噢，凯蒂，给你
- It's Cady. - Oh, Cady, here you go.
你的一个，格雷琴・维纳斯没有，拜
One for you. And none for Gretchen Wieners. Bye.
谁给你的？
Who's that from?
“作为挚友非常荣幸，爱你的，莉贾娜”
"Thanks for being such a great friend. Love, Regina."
写得真好
That's so sweet.
好了，回到凯撒这来
OK, back to Caesar.
一旦格雷琴发觉莉贾娜在生她的气
Once Gretchen thought Regina was mad at her,
秘密就会开始泄漏
the secrets started pouring out.
我们要做的就是等待时机
All I had to do was wait for one we could use.
谢谢大家
Thank you.
欢迎来到北岸高中冬季业余歌手演唱会
Welcome to the North Shore High School winter talent show.
让我听听大家的掌声吧
Let me hear you make some noise.
好了，安静吧
All right, settle down.
我们第一位歌手自称是成长中的巨星
Our first act calls himself a star on the rise.
我们欢迎戴米恩
Let's hear it for Damian.
别看我
Don't look at me.
Every day is so wonderful
我是说，为什么莉贾娜送你糖果棒而不送我呢？
I mean, why would Regina send you guys candy canes and not me?
或许是她忘给你了
Maybe she forgot about you.
是的，莉贾娜最近有些古怪
Yeah, Regina has been acting kind of weird lately.
我是说，是不是什么事情令她烦恼？
I mean, is something bothering her?
呃，我是说，要是你的意思是
Well, I mean, her parents totally don't sleep in the same bed anymore,
她父母已经彻底分居了
if that's what you mean.
噢，上帝，别告诉她我说的话
Oh, my God. Don't tell her I told you that.
I am beautiful in every single way
Yes, words can't bring me down
Don't you bring me down today
我是说，别见怪
I mean, no offense,
为什么她会送你一个糖果棒呢？
but why would she send you a candy cane?
她不是很喜欢你啊
She doesn't even like you that much.
或许她察觉我行为诡异
Maybe she feels weird around me
因为我是唯一知道她隆鼻的人
because I'm the only person that knows about her nose job.
噢，上帝，你当作没听到好吗
Oh, my God. Pretend you didn't hear that.
Yo, yo, yo
All you sucker MCs Ain't got nothing on me
From my grades to my lines You can't touch Kevin G
I'm a Mathlete So nerd is inferred
But forget what you heard I'm like James Bond the Third
Shaken not stirred I'm Kevin Gnapoor
The G is silent When I sneak in your door
And make love to your woman On the bathroom floor
I don't play it like Shaggy You'll know it was me
Because the next time you see her She'll be like
- Kevin G! - 谢谢，凯文，够了
- Kevin G! - Thank you, Kevin, that's enough.
大伙儿，假日愉快
Happy holidays, everybody.
凯文・纳泊尔和“三人动力”
K.G. and the Power of Three.
有意思
That was something.
他们还在跳你的原创舞蹈，你难受吗？
Does it bother you that they still use your original choreography?
住嘴
Shut up.
该死
Damn.
- 怎么？ - 我想在外面看你...
- What? - I'd rather see you out there
抖动你那玩意儿
shaking that thing.
格雷琴，和凯蒂换一边
Gretchen, switch sides with Cady.
可我一直在你左边的啊
But I'm always on your left.
那是我们只有三人的时候 现在最高的应该站在中间
That was when there were three of us, and now the tallest go in the middle.
那整个舞蹈都会反过来
But the whole dance will be backwards.
我一直在你左边的
I'm always on your left.
你快激怒我最后一根神经了，快换过来
And right now you're getting on my last nerve. Switch.
最后，大家欢迎圣诞大作
And finally, please welcome to the stage
《圣诞铃声响》亮相舞台
Santa's Helpers doing "Jingle Bell Rock".
Jingle bell, jingle bell Jingle bell rock
Jingle bells swing And jingle bells ring
Snowing and blowing Up bushels of fun
Now the jingle hop has begun
Jingle bell, jingle bell Jingle bell rock
Jingle bells chime In jingle bell time
Dancing and prancing In Jingle Bell Square
In the fr...
詹森？
Jason?
What a bright time It's the right time
To rock the night away
Jingle bell time Is a swell time
To go riding in a one-horse sleigh
Giddyap jingle horse Pick up your feet
Jingle around the clock
Mix and mingle in a jingling beat
That's the jingle bell
That's the jingle bell rock
这是跳得的最好的一次！
That was the best it ever went!
- 真太棒了 - 有口红
- That was awesome. - Lip gloss.
- 嘿，干得好，非洲人 - 谢谢
- Hey, good job, Africa. - Thanks.
凯蒂脸都红了，噢，上帝
Cady's blushing. Oh, my God.
- 你一定爱上了那家伙 - 不，我没有
- You totally have a crush on that guy. - No, I don't.
难怪你想加入数奥队呢
That's why you wanted to join the Mathletes.
数奥队？你讨厌数学呀
Mathletes? You hate math.
看她脸多红
Look how red she is.
你爱上他了，他就是在恭维你
You love him. And he totally complimented you.
太诱惑了
That is so fetch.
格雷琴，别再讲什么“诱惑”了
Gretchen, stop trying to make "fetch" happen.
再也不要听到
It's not going to happen.
“为什么凯撒要开始像巨人一样跺脚呢？
"Why should Caesar get to stomp around like a giant
“而被他的大脚踩过后，其他人都无法避免被踩扁？
"while the rest of us try not to get smushed under his big feet?
“为什么凯撒如此伟大？
"What's so great about Caesar?
“布鲁图和凯撒一样聪明啊
"Brutus is just as cute as Caesar.
“好，布鲁图和凯撒一样聪明
"OK, Brutus is just as smart as Caesar.
“人们喜爱布鲁图只是由于他们喜爱凯撒
"People totally like Brutus just as much as they like Caesar.
“对于一个欲作万人之君的人来说
"And when did it become OK for one person
“这何时才会成立呢？
"to be the boss of everybody?
“因为那不是罗马的本来面目
"Because that's not what Rome is about!
“我们完全应当中伤凯撒
"We should totally just stab Caesar!"
格雷琴・维纳斯已被击破
Gretchen Wieners had cracked.
好，如果你知道她有多下贱
OK, if you even knew how mean she really is.
你知道她们不允许我戴耳环，对吧？
You know that I'm not allowed to wear hoop earrings, right?
是的，两年前，她告诉我，耳环是属于她的
Yeah. Two years ago, she told me that hoop earrings were her thing
于是我就再也不能佩带了
and that I wasn't allowed to wear them anymore.
然后到了光明节，我父母给我买了
And then for my Hanukkah, my parents got me this pair
这对真正值钱的白金耳环
of really expensive white-gold hoops.
我却装作一点也不喜欢
And I had to pretend like I didn't even like them,
太悲哀了
and it was so sad.
你知道她对亚伦不忠吗？
And you know she cheats on Aaron?
是的，每个周四，他认为她在为周六而准备
Yes. Every Thursday he thinks she's doing SAT prep.
但事实上，她却与谢恩・阿曼在
But really, she's hooking up with Shane Oman in the projection room
礼堂上面的放映室里缠绵
above the auditorium,
我对别人只字不提，因为...
and I never told anybody that, because...
...我是如此真挚的朋友
...I'm such a good friend.
意外之喜，格雷琴的秘密让计划又重新开始运转
Jackpot. Gretchen's secret had put the plan back in motion.
圣诞节后，我们每周四都试图
After Christmas break, we tried every Thursday
帮助亚伦当场揭穿莉贾娜
to help Aaron catch Regina in the act.
（游泳队的训练将在礼堂上的放映室进行）
嗨
Hey.
嗨，什么事？
Hey, what's up?
我的钱包！
My purse!
看上去他正朝礼堂
Looks like he's headed for the projection room
上面的放映室跑去！
above the auditorium!
卡尔教练？
Coach Carr?
Trang Pak？
Trang Pak?
伙计，为什么认为我们能行呢？
Guys, why did we think we could do this?
我们只是业余的
We're amateurs.
不，我们只是需要重新想想，放开我们的思维
No, we just have to regroup. Think outside our box.
卡尔丁棒是什么?
What are Kalteen bars?
是神奇的瑞典营养棒
They're these weird Swedish nutrition bars.
我母亲曾用它来帮助非洲的孩子增加重量
My mom used to give them to the kids in Africa to help them gain weight.
这些神奇的营养棒是我妈妈用来减肥的
They're these weird nutrition bars my mom uses to lose weight.
给我
Give me it.
都是用瑞典文写的
It's all in, like, Swedish or something.
对啊，你知道，有神奇的东西在里面
Yeah, you know, there's some weird ingredient in them
在美国还不合法
that's not legal in the U.S. yet.
- 麻黄素？ - 不是
- Ephedrine? - No.
- 酚妥拉明 - 不
- Phentermine. - No.
它燃烧脂肪，燃烧所有的脂肪
It burns carbs. It just burns up all your carbs.
我真想减轻3磅
I really wanna lose 3 pounds.
哦，上帝，你们在谈什么？
Oh, my God, what are you talking about?
你很瘦了
You're so skinny.
闭嘴
Shut up.
把这个神奇棒给莉贾娜
The weird thing about hanging out with Regina
让我可以恨她，同时
was that I could hate her, and at the same time,
还要她喜欢我
I still wanted her to like me.
好，你的眉毛棒极了
OK. You have really good eyebrows.
- 谢谢 - 让开
- Thanks. - Move.
和格雷琴一样，莉贾娜对她越坏
Same with Gretchen. The meaner Regina was to her,
格雷琴越想将莉贾娜赢回来
the more Gretchen tried to win Regina back.
她知道在“魔鬼身材”中会更加好
She knew it was better to be in The Plastics, hating life
宁愿讨厌，也不要离开
than to not be in at all.
因为在“魔鬼身材”就会受人瞩目
Because being with The Plastics was like being famous.
人们会总是看着你
People looked at you all the time,
每个人都会知道你的事情
and everybody just knew stuff about you.
那个新来的女孩是从非洲来的
That new girl moved here from Africa.
我看到凯蒂・海伦穿着军短裤和拖鞋
I saw Cady Heron wearing Army pants and flip-flops,
所以我买了军短裤和拖鞋
so I bought Army pants and flip-flops.
凯蒂很辣
That Cady girl is hot.
她可能比莉贾娜・乔治还辣
She might even be hotter than Regina George.
我听说莉贾娜・乔治又在和亚伦・塞缪尔约会了
I hear Regina George is dating Aaron Samuels again.
有人看到两人在克里斯・埃瑟尔的万圣节晚会上亲热
The two were seen canoodling at Chris Eisel's Halloween party.
他们从来就没分开
They've been inseparable ever since.
我着了魔
I was a woman possessed.
我花了80％的时间谈论莉贾娜
I spent about 80 percent of my time talking about Regina.
剩下20％的时间
And the other 20 percent of the time,
我祈祷有人能阻止她
I was praying for someone else to bring her up
我就可以更多的谈论她
so I could talk about her more.
如果你仔细看，她已经没那么好看
She's not even that good-looking if you really look at her.
我不知道，现在她正在变胖
I don't know. Now that's she's getting fatter,
她像个大水壶
she's got pretty big jugs.
我能听到人们越来越讨厌我
I could hear people getting bored with me.
但是我不能停止，就像呕吐一样，不停的讨论
But I couldn't stop. It just kept coming up like word vomit.
我想，如果你剃光她所有的头发 她会看上去像个英国男人
I have this theory that if you cut all her hair off, she'd look like a British man.
是，我知道，你以前和我说过
Yeah, I know. You told me that one before.
嘿，我有一场艺术秀
Hey, I'm having an art show.
你为什么不花一个晚上告别你的双重生活
So why don't you take a night off from your double life.
- 我想你去看 - 酷
- I want you to see it. - Coolness.
什么味道？
What is that smell?
哦，莉贾娜给了我些香水
Oh, Regina gave me some perfume.
你闻起来象个雏妓
You smell like a baby prostitute.
多谢
Thanks.
同时，我在找任何借口和亚伦说话
Meanwhile, I was finding any excuse I could to talk to Aaron.
我不知道这怎么做，你会吗？
I don't get this. Do you get any of this?
干得好，凯蒂
Nice job, Cady.
看来你似乎懂了
Kind of seems like you get it.
如果我想继续下去，我就得犯点错
If I was gonna keep this going, I was gonna have to really commit.
没做好
Not your best.
该死，非洲人，怎么了？
Damn, Africa, what happened?
- 怎么样？ - 不好
- How'd you do? - Not so good.
你知道，我想我需要个辅导
You know, I think I need a tutor.
我来教你，如果你想放学后在一起
I'll tutor you, if you ever wanna get together after school or something.
莉贾娜会介意吗？
Do you think Regina would mind?
不会，你们是朋友
No. You guys are friends.
好，或许我们可以不告诉她
Well, maybe we just won't tell her.
那么，你是怎么得到这个的？
So, what did you get for this one?
嗯，我第一次做，得到一个零
Well, the first time I did it, I got a zero.
- 错 - 但是当我检查的时候，我得到了...
- Wrong. - But then when I checked it, I got...
- ...一 - 对了
-...one. - There you go.
我也得到一
I got one too.
对，你不得不检查几次
Yeah, you have to check it because sometimes the product
因为有时候两个负数的乘积会是个正数
of two negative integers is a positive number.
对，象负四乘以负六
Yeah, like negative four and negative six.
对，很好
That's right. That's good.
你是个好老师
Well, you're a good tutor.
瞧，我不能这样做
Man, look, l... I can't do this.
- 这对莉贾娜不公平 - 你为什么喜欢她？
- It's not fair to Regina. - Why do you like her?
瞧，我知道有时候她确实有点卑鄙，但是...
Look, I know she can be really mean sometimes, but...
- 那你为什么喜欢她？ - 你为什么？
- Then why do you like her? - Why do you?
嘿，任何人都有好有坏，对吗？
Look, there's good and bad to everybody. Right?
莉贾娜只是...
Regina's just...
- 她只是更超前一点 - 哦，不，又要来了
- She's just more up-front about it. - Oh, no. It was coming up.
呕吐的感觉，我不是这个意思，但...
The word vomit. I didn't mean to say it, but...
她在骗你！
She's cheating on you!
什么？
What?
他有没有说为什么？
Did he say why?
有人告诉他谢恩・阿曼的事了
Somebody told him about Shane Oman.
谁？
Who?
他说是棒球队的
He said some guy on the baseball team.
棒球队？
Baseball team?
我为他付出了一切 遇见他时，我似乎还是个处女
I gave him everything. I was half a virgin when I met him.
想不想做些有趣的事？
You wanna do something fun?
去吃粟米片？
You wanna go to Taco Bell?
我不能吃粟米片，我正在节食
I can't go to Taco Bell, I'm on an all-carb diet.
上帝，克伦，你真是个傻瓜！
God, Karen, you are so stupid!
莉贾娜，等等，跟我说
Regina, wait. Talk to me.
- 没有人理解我 - 我理解
- Nobody understands me. - I understand you.
你不傻，克伦
You're not stupid, Karen.
不，我傻，真的
No. I am, actually.
什么事我都会搞砸
I'm failing almost everything.
肯定有你行的事
Well, there must be something you're good at.
我能把整个拳头放进嘴里
I can put my whole fist in my mouth.
想不想看？
Wanna see?
不，不用了
No. That's OK.
还有其它的吗？
Anything else?
我能通灵
I'm kind of psychic.
我有第五感
I have a fifth sense.
- 什么意思？ - 好像我拥有ESPN或什么的
- What do you mean? - It's like I have ESPN or something.
我的胸部能够知道什么时候下雨
My breasts can always tell when it's gonna rain.
真的？太神奇了
Really? That's amazing.
对，它们能知道什么时候下雨
Well, they can tell when it's raining.
我不得不承认，我有点怕了
I have to admit, I was mildly horrified
当亚伦没有马上让我作他的女朋友
when Aaron didn't immediately ask me to be his girlfriend.
我的意思是，我知道他很难过 但是他需要多少时间呢？
I mean, I know he was sad, but how much time did he need?
莉贾娜已经转移注意力了
Regina had moved on.
你们需要什么吗？要来点小吃吗？
Do you guys need anything? Some snacks?
避孕套要吗？
A condom?
告诉我，哦，上帝爱你们
Let me know. Oh, God love you.
但总之，计划进展顺利
But overall, the plan was going pretty well.
亚伦踢掉了莉贾娜，而她还不知道
Aaron had dumped Regina, and she was unknowingly
每天会摄入5000卡的热量
eating 5,000 calories a day.
是时候把注意力转到贱人死党上了
It was time to turn our attention to the army of skanks.
最后
And finally, the nominees for Spring Fling Queen are as follows:
春季狂欢节王后的人选是：
莉贾娜・乔治
Regina George.
格雷琴・维纳斯
Gretchen Wieners.
珍尼斯・伊安
Janis Ian.
怎么会这样？
What is happening to the world?
最后一名候选人...
And the final nominee...
我情不自禁，太容易了
I couldn't help myself. It was so easy.
...是凯蒂・海伦
...is Cady Heron.
戴米安，你把我也放进去了？ 这不是计划的一部分
Damian, you put me in there too? That's not part of the plan.
我没有把你放进去
I didn't put you in there.
你的意思是，我是真正的候选人？
You mean I'm really nominated?
一月份，莉贾娜在一家叫1-3-5的店
In January, Regina had put a Spring Fling dress on hold
定了件春季狂欢节的礼服
at a store called 1-3-5.
但作为“魔鬼身材”的一员，在真买之前
But being Plastic, she needed our advice
她需要我们的建议
before she could actually buy it.
谁能帮我拉上拉链吗？
Can someone zip me up?
- 拉不上 - 这是5号的
- It won't close. - It's a 5.
一定是标错了
OK, it must be marked wrong.
凯蒂, 我吃的都是卡尔丁棒，骗人的
Cady, all I've been eating are these Kalteen bars. They suck.
不，不，就是这样起作用的
No, no, this is just how they work.
这是你体内水的分量
This is all your water weight.
你会先发胖，然后会一下子减掉10磅
First you bloat, and then you drop 10 pounds like that:
呃，卡尔丁棒已经燃烧你所有的油脂
Well, the Kalteen bars have burned up all your carbs,
而你现在体内都是水分
and now your body's just running on water.
一旦水分去掉，就只是肌肉了
But once the water's gone, then you'll be all muscle.
这在标签上都说了
It explains it all on the label.
你懂瑞典文？
You know Swedish?
是，非洲人都懂
Yeah, everyone in Africa can read Swedish.
小姐，有大一号的吗？
Ma'am, do you have this in the next size up?
对不起，我们只有1、3、5号
Sorry. We only carry sizes 1, 3 and 5.
你可以试一下老年装
You could try Sears.
凯蒂
Cady.
我要你父母签字，以便他们知道你不及格
I need your parents to sign this so they know that you're failing.
不及格？
Failing?
你知道你的试卷有多奇怪，凯蒂
You know what's weird about your quizzes, Cady,
所有的运算都是对的，只有答案错了
is that all the work is right and just the answers are wrong.
- 真的？ - 真的
- Really? - Really.
凯蒂，我知道，你现在最重要
Cady, I know that having a boyfriend
的事可能是谈恋爱
may seem like the most important thing in the world right now,
但没必要为了讨男生的欢心，而荒废学业
but you don't have to dumb yourself down to get guys to like you.
- 你怎么知道？ - 我知道
- How would you know? - I know,
“我怎么会知道”，对不对？
"How would I know", right?
我离婚了，挣脱了这个枷锁
I'm divorced. I'm broke from getting divorced.
唯一到我家拜访过的男人是大通威士公司的兰迪
The only guy that ever calls my house is Randy from Chase Visa.
你知道为什么吗？
And you know why?
因为我爱强迫，总是强迫人
Because I'm a pusher. I push people.
我强迫丈夫到法律学院，真是失败
I pushed my husband into law school. That was a bust.
我强迫自己找三份工作
I pushed myself into working three jobs.
而现在我要强迫你
And now I'm gonna push you
因为我知道你实际上很聪明
because I know you're smarter than this.
谢谢，诺布里夫人，如果我能通过什么途径
Thanks, Ms. Norbury. And if there's anything I can do
挣的额外的学分，请告诉我
for extra credit, please let me know.
哦，我会的
Oh, I will.
我恨她！我是说，她故意让我不合格
I hate her! I mean, she's totally failing me on purpose
因为我没有参加那愚蠢的数奥队！
because I didn't join those stupid Mathletes!
她太奇怪了
She was so queer.
她说“我爱强迫别人，凯蒂，我爱强迫人”
She was like, "I'm a pusher, Cady. I'm a pusher."
什么意思？
What does that even mean?
- 很可能是贩毒的？ - 也许
- Like a drug pusher? - Probably.
或许吧，她说她有三份工作
She said she works three jobs.
你知道，我打赌她在路边卖毒品
You know, I bet she sells drugs on the side
来偿还她可悲的离婚
to pay for her pathetic divorce.
甜心，写出来吧
You let it out, honey.
写在书里
Put it in the book.
我知道看上去我象个婊子
I know it may look like I'd become a bitch,
但那只是因为我在扮一个婊子
but that's only because I was acting like a bitch.
嘿，昨天我打你电话，你怎么没回我？
Hey, I called you last night. How come you didn't call me back?
噢，我很忙，抱歉
Oh, I got busy. Sorry.
那周末你需要乘车去我的艺术展？
So you need a ride to my art show this weekend?
不，我得和父母去麦迪逊
No. I have to go to Madison with my parents.
真抱歉
I'm so sorry.
嗯，今晚想去看电影吗？
Well, you wanna watch a movie tonight?
不行，今晚我要蓄谋对“魔鬼身材” 发动决定性的攻击
Can't. I'm doing major Plastic sabotage tonight.
但是我们今晚没有任何计划
But we don't have anything planned for tonight.
哦，是我自己计划的
Oh, I planned this one on my own.
爱你们，再见
Love you. Bye.
格雷琴认为你在生她的气
Gretchen thinks you're mad at her
因为她参加了春季狂欢会王后的竞选
because she's running for Spring Fling Queen.
噢，上帝，我没生她气，我是担心她
Oh, my God, I'm not mad at her. I'm worried about her.
我认为她被提名是有人在捉弄她
I think somebody nominated her as a joke or something.
如果没人投她票，她会彻底崩溃
And when nobody votes for her, she's gonna have a total meltdown.
那还有谁来安慰她？我
And who's gonna have to take care of her? Me.
所以你认为不会有人投她票？
So you don't think anyone will vote for her?
凯蒂，她不漂亮
Cady, she's not pretty.
这听上去挺糟，但是不管怎么样
I mean, that sounds bad, but whatever.
春季狂欢会的王后都是很漂亮的
The Spring Fling Queen is always pretty.
而疯狂的是，那应该属于克伦
And the crazy thing is is that it should be Karen,
但是人们已经忘记了她，因为她是个荡妇
but people forget about her because she's such a slut.
总之，我要挂了，我要上床了
Anyway, I gotta go. I'm going to bed.
呃，她没有生你的气
Well, she's not mad at you.
- 别挂 - 你还好吗？
- Hold on. - Are you OK?
- 喂？ - 如果有人说你坏话
- Hello? - If someone said something bad
你希望我告诉你，对吗？
about you, you'd want me to tell you, right?
不
- No. - What if it was someone
如果是你认为是朋友的人呢？
you thought was your friend?
你想说什么...？ 别挂，我换条线
What are you...? Hold on. Other line.
- 我再也憋不住了 - 祝好运，格雷琴
- I'm not taking this anymore. - Good for you, Gretch.
- 喂？ - 我们出去吧
- Hello? - Let's go out.
好，别挂，我和格雷琴在另外一条线上
OK. Hold on. I'm on the other line with Gretchen.
别叫上格雷琴，她在乱说话
Don't invite Gretchen. She's driving me nuts.
- 别挂 - 好，快点
- Hold on. - OK, hurry up.
我是莉贾娜
It's Regina.
她想和我今晚出去，但是说不要告诉你
She wants to hang out with me tonight, but she told me not to tell you.
不要和她出去
Do not hang out with her.
- 为什么？ - 你不会希望我告诉你的
- Why? - You don't want me to tell you.
你可以给我说，别挂
You can tell me. Hold on.
哦，上帝，她真讨厌
Oh, my God, she's so annoying.
谁？
Who is?
- 你是谁？ - 格雷琴
- Who's this? - Gretchen.
好，别挂
Right. Hold on.
- 哦，上帝，她真讨厌 - 我知道，别叫她就行了
- Oh, my God, she's so annoying. - I know. Just get rid of her.
好，什么？
OK. What is it?
莉贾娜说每个人都恨你，因为你是个荡妇
Regina says everyone hates you because you're such a slut.
她这样说了？
She said that?
你不是从我这里听到的
You didn't hear it from me.
- 有点讨厌啊，格雷琴 - 不管怎样，她有权知道
- Little harsh, Gretch. - Whatever. She has a right to know.
我不能出去
I can't go out.
我病了
I'm sick.
切，你这个贱货
Boo. You whore.
莉贾娜,
Regina,
我们要和你谈谈
we have to talk to you.
黄油含脂肪吗？
Is butter a carb?
是的
Yes.
莉贾娜，你穿着运动裤
Regina, you're wearing sweatpants.
今天是礼拜一啊
It's Monday.
- 那又怎样？ - 违反规则啦
- So? - So that's against the rules
你不能和我们坐一起了
and you can't sit with us.
无所谓啊，规则是可变的嘛
Whatever. Those rules aren't real.
那天我穿背心，规则就不能变？
They were real that day I wore a vest.
- 因为背心令人讨厌 - 你不能和我们坐一起！
- Because that vest was disgusting. - You can't sit with us!
现在只有运动裤我穿着合身了
These sweatpants are all that fits me right now.
好
Fine.
你可以走回家，婊子
You can walk home, bitches.
瞧你怎么在走路，肥屁股！
Watch where you're going, fat-ass!
格雷琴和克伦整个下午都跟着我
Gretchen and Karen followed me around all afternoon.
- 那我们周末干什么？ - 是啊，周末干什么？
- So, what are we doing this weekend? - Yeah, what are we doing?
哦，我要和父母去麦迪逊
Oh, I have to go to Madison with my parents.
什么...？
What...?
我们都买好票了
We have tickets for this thing.
- 什么？ - 什么？
- What? - What?
我会是新的蜂后吗？
Was I the new queen bee?
我会去努力争取一下的
I can try and get out of it.
- 好的 - 好，好
- Yeah. - Yeah. Yeah.
因为我告诉了我的朋友珍尼斯 我会去看她的艺术展
Because I told my friend Janis I'd go to her art show.
我们几个月前就买好票了
We've had these tickets for months.
但你喜欢雷迪斯密斯来的黑斧乐队
You love Ladysmith Black Mambazo.
但是她是我的朋友，而且我已经答应她了
But she's my friend, and I made her a promise.
我想凯蒂够大了，可以独自过夜了
I think Cady's old enough to spend one night on her own.
我已经学会怎么控制我周围的人了
I had learned how to control everyone around me.
嘿，明晚在我家有个小型的聚会
Hey. I'm having a small get-together at my house tomorrow night.
- 莉贾娜去吗？ - 不，你认为我是个傻瓜吗？
- Is Regina going? - No. Do you think I'm an idiot?
不，去的都是些很酷的家伙
No, it's just gonna be a few cool people,
你最好也是其中一员，小可爱
and you better be one of them, byotch.
- 好，我会去的 - 说定了
- Fine, I'll go. - Shut up.
我喜欢你穿这件衣服
I love that shirt on you.
亚伦・塞缪尔就要来我家参加聚会了
Aaron Samuels was going to be in my house at my party.
一切都应该很完美
Everything had to be perfect.
就在这个时候，当亚伦看到我
And this time when Aaron saw me,
我本不应该穿着这么可笑的衣服
I wouldn't be caught in some ridiculous costume.
嘿，朋友们
Hey, guys.
- 你看上去太棒了！ - 你看上去太棒了！
- You look awesome! - You look awesome!
我知道，是吗？
I know, right?
好，我有够八个人的奶酪和饼干
OK, so I got enough cheese and crackers for eight people.
你们认为那够了吗？
Do you think that's enough?
- 够了 - 是的，噢，够了
- Yeah. - Yeah. Oh, yeah.
好
OK.
根本不够
It was not enough.
不知怎么，我办聚会的事传了出去
Somehow, the word had gotten out about my small get-together.
詹森和泰勒・威德尔在这儿
Jason is here with Taylor Wedell.
他是让她来气你的
He's just using her to make you mad.
- 你们看到亚伦了吗？ - 没有
- Have you guys seen Aaron yet? - No.
哥们，放《罗摩衍那猴子圣歌》吧
Dude, put on "The Ramayana Monkey Chant".
- 我认识你吗？ - 迪克！怎么了，小妞儿？
- Do I know you? - Deek! What up, dog?
她认为她可以举行晚会不邀请我？
She thinks she's gonna have a party and not invite me?
- 她认为她是谁？ - 你说得对，甜心
- Who does she think she is? - You're right, hon.
可能是我教她的吧，你知道我得意思？
I, like, invented her, you know what I mean?
詹森
Jason.
我要和你说一下
I have to talk to you.
什么？
Whatever.
- 我爱你 - 我知道，我知道
- I love you. - I know, I know.
嘿！把那放下！
Hey! Put that down!
亚伦和我吹了？
Was Aaron blowing me off?
什么事？格雷琴来找我谈
What's up? Gretchen came to talk to me.
- 哦，不要 - 瞧
- Oh, no. - Look,
我并不想伤害你的感情 但我只和有色女人约会
I don't wanna hurt your feelings, but I only date women of color.
我要去小便
I have to pee.
出去
Get out.
- 嗨 - 嗨
- Hey. - Hey.
我到处找你
I've been looking for you everywhere.
我也是
Me too.
你看上去...
You look...
- 新衣服？ - 谢谢
- New clothes? - Thanks.
想到楼下去吗？
You wanna go downstairs?
不，不，就呆在这吧
No, no. Let's stay here.
感谢你今晚让我来这
Thanks for getting me to come out tonight.
是的，当然，没问题
Yeah, sure, no problem.
我浪费了太多时间迷恋莉贾娜
I wasted too much time being pissed off at Regina.
别再撒谎了
No more liars.
我从不骗你
I would never lie to you.
我知道，我知道
I know, I know.
尽管...
Although...
好了，听着，我是说，我对你撒过一次谎
OK, listen. I mean, I did lie to you once,
但是当我说的时候你大笑，所以...
but you're totally gonna laugh when I tell you, so...
告诉我什么？
Tell me what?
我假装数学不好，这样你就可以教我
I pretended to be bad at math so that you'd help me.
但事实是，我不是真的数学不好
But the thing is, I'm not really bad at math.
我的数学真的很好，而你却挺差的
I'm actually really good at math. You're kind of bad at math.
总之，现在我不及格，有趣吧？
Anyways, now I'm failing. Isn't that funny?
等一下，你故意不及格？太笨了
Wait. You're failing on purpose? That's stupid.
不，不是故意，你知道，只是...
No. Not on purpose. Just, you know...
我想找个理由和你说话
I just wanted a reason to talk to you.
为什么你不和我直说呢？
So why didn't you just talk to me?
呃...因为我不能，因为莉贾娜
Well, because I couldn't. Because of Regina.
因为你是她的...
Because you were her property...
- 她的？ - 不，不讲了，不是她的...
- Her property? - No. Shut up. Not her property...
不，不要叫我闭嘴
No, don't tell me to shut up.
- 我不是... - 上帝，你知道吗？
- I wasn't... - God, you know what?
你简直就是莉贾娜的克隆
You are just like a clone of Regina.
哦，不，不，听我说，你不在听我说...
Oh, no, no, listen to me. You're not listening to me...
哦，不，又来了，要吐出来了 不，等一下...
Oh, no. It was coming up again. Word vomit. No, wait a minute...
- 你们在干吗？！ - 真要吐了
- What is this?! - Actual vomit.
亚伦！
Aaron!
亚伦，等等！...
Aaron, wait! Just...
好，打我电话
OK. Call me.
- 哦，上帝 - 你这个肮脏的小骗子
- Oh, God. - You dirty little liar.
抱歉，我来解释
I'm sorry. I can explain.
解释你怎么忘了邀请我们来参加你的晚会？
Explain how you forgot to invite us to your party?
珍尼斯，我不停车了，我有宵禁令的
Janis, I cannot stop this car. I have a curfew.
你知道我不能邀请你 我得装作“魔鬼身材”的一员
You know I couldn't invite you. I had to pretend to be Plastic.
嘿，朋友，你别再装了
Hey, buddy, you're not pretending anymore.
你就是“魔鬼身材”的一员 冰冷的、耀眼的、顽固的“魔鬼身材”
You're Plastic. Cold, shiny, hard Plastic.
宵禁令是凌晨1点，现在是1:10
Curfew, 1 a.m. It is now 1 :1 0.
你度过了一个绝好的夜晚？
Did you have an awesome time?
喝着绝好的饮料，听着绝好的音乐
Did you drink awesome shooters and listen to awesome music,
然后坐在一起分享彼此的精彩？
and then just sit around and soak up each other's awesomeness?
就是你让我变成这样的
You're the one who made me like this
这样就可以利用我来报八年级的仇
so you could use me for your eighth-grade revenge.
上帝！瞧，至少我和莉贾娜・乔治知道我们贱
God! See, at least me and Regina George know we're mean.
你却装作天真无邪的说 “噢，我以前住在非洲
You try to act like you're so innocent. Like, "Oh, I used to live in Africa
有很多小鸟，小猴子”
"with all the little birdies and the little monkeys."
你知道为什么？你爱我不是我的错！
You know what? It's not my fault you're in love with me or something!
- 什么？！ - 噢，不，她没有
- What?! - Oh, no she did not!
看见了吗？你们“魔鬼身材”就是这样
See? That is the thing with you Plastics.
你以为所有的人都迷恋你
You think that everybody is in love with you,
而实际上，所有的人都恨你
when actually, everybody hates you.
比如亚伦・塞缪尔
Like Aaron Samuels, for example.
他和莉贾娜分手，知道是为什么吗？
He broke up with Regina and guess what.
他也不想要你
He still doesn't want you.
那你为什么还和莉贾娜鬼混呢 凯蒂？我来告诉你原因吧
So why are you still messing with Regina, Cady? I'll tell you why.
因为你是个贱女孩！你是个婊子！
Because you are a mean girl! You're a bitch!
拿去，你拿着这个，获奖了
Here. You can have this. It won a prize.
我希望我的粉色的衬衫回来
And I want my pink shirt back!
我想要回我的粉色上衣！
I want my pink shirt back!
甜心，慢点
Hon, slow down.
似乎我再也不能相信任何人了
It's like I can't trust anyone anymore.
你为什么吃卡尔丁棒？
Why are you eating a Kalteen bar?
- 我很饿 - 老兄，我恨那个东西
- I'm starving. - Man, I hate those things.
卡尔教练叫我们想增重时就吃这个
Coach Carr makes us eat those when we wanna move up a weight class.
什么？
What?
它们可以让你发疯般的增重
They make you gain weight like crazy.
妈妈...
Mother...
这个女的是我见过的
This girl is the nastiest skank bitch
最下流的婊子
I've ever met.
不要相信她，她是个臭荡妇！
Do not trust her. She is a fugly slut!
（莉贾娜・乔治）
我在女厕所里找到了这个 这太下贱了，杜瓦尔先生
I found it in the girls' bathroom. It's so mean, Mr. Duvall.
这是真的？
Is this true?
Trang Pak和卡尔教练？
Trang Pak made out with Coach Carr?
上帝
Good Lord.
上面说什么？“凯特琳・考辛是个...”？
What's that say? "Kaitlyn Caussin is a..."?
胖妓女
Fat whore.
好，冷静，乔治小姐
OK, calm down, Miss George.
为什么会有人写这个东西？太下贱了
Why would someone write that? That's just so mean.
不要担心，我们会查出来是谁干的
Don't worry, we're gonna find out who did it.
整个学校只有三个女的不在里面
There's only three girls in the whole school who aren't in it.
你们这个年纪，性欲旺盛
At your age, you're gonna be having a lot of urges.
你们想除去衣衫，相互触碰
You're gonna want to take off your clothes and touch each other.
但是如果你们彼此接触，就会得性病，死去
But if you do touch each other, you will get chlamydia. And die.
卡尔教练
Coach Carr.
凯蒂・海伦，你去趟校长办公室
Cady Heron, they wanna see you in the principal's office.
好了，衣原体，K-L-A...
All right, chlamydia. K-L-A...
这里，海伦小姐
In here, Miss Heron.
- 什么事？ - 请坐，海伦小姐
- What's going on? - Have a seat, Miss Heron.
- 你以前看到过这个吗？ - 没有
- Have you ever seen this before? - No.
我的意思是，是的，我看到过 但这不是我的
I mean, yes, I've seen it before, but it's not mine.
你最好说实话，海伦小姐
You better get your story straight, Miss Heron,
因为我不想在这儿浪费时间
because I'm not messing around here.
这不是我们的，是莉贾娜的
It's not ours, it's Regina's.
对，她想把这弄得看上去是我们的 但是，真的，是她写的
Yeah, she's trying to make it look like we wrote it, but really, she wrote it.
维纳斯小姐，莉贾娜为什么 会说自己是“臭荡妇”呢？
Miss Wieners, why would Regina refer to herself as a "fugly slut"?
史密斯小姐，现在不是笑的时候
Miss Smith, this is no time to be laughing.
我们现在就把这件事搞清楚
We're gonna get to the bottom of this right now.
也许我们不在书里，是因为大家都喜欢我们
Maybe we're not in that book, because everybody likes us.
我不想因为受人喜欢而遭指责
And I don't wanna be punished for being well-liked.
另外，我想我父亲，果馅卷的发明者
And I don't think my father, the inventor of Toaster Strudel,
听说后也不会太高兴
would be too pleased to hear about this.
“和烂人有染”？
"Made out with a hot dog"?
哦，上帝，就一次啊！
Oh, my God, that was one time!
“道恩・施韦策是个肥臀”？ 谁会写这个？
"Dawn Schweitzer has a huge ass"? Who would write that?
谁不会写？
Who wouldn't write that?
“Trang Pak和卡尔教练有染”？
"Trang Pak made out with Coach Carr"?
孙金顶也是
And so did Sun Jin Dinh.
你个小荡妇！
你才是荡妇！
嘿！嘿！安静！好了，嘿
Hey! Hey! Settle down! All right, hey.
不，你们别相互推攘...
No. You do not push and sh...
（...莎伦・诺贝利，数学老师... ...是个悲惨的老毒贩）
你还有什么想说的吗？
Do you have anything else you wanna say?
不，我无法回答任何问题
No, I can't answer any more questions
直到我父母或律师在场
until I have a parent or lawyer present.
史密斯小姐？
Miss Smith?
无论是谁写的，可能都 不会想到有人会看到？
Whoever wrote it probably didn't think anyone would ever see it?
我不希望其他人看到这个
I hope that nobody else ever does see it.
妈妈，你能接我走吗？我好怕
Mom, can you pick me up? I'm scared.
- “珍尼斯・伊安，同性恋？” - 这是原件
- "Janis lan, dyke"? - That's original.
- “行为夸张”？！ - 嘿！
- "Too gay to function"?! - Hey!
这只有我这么说
That's only OK when I say it.
- 你写的？ - 不，我发誓！
- Did you write this? - No, I swear!
- 那你告诉了别人！ - 她讲过！
- Then you told somebody! - She told!
- 你个小贱人！ - 你是个婊子！
- You little bitch! - You're a bitch!
好！把头拧下来！
Yeah! Take your top off!
- 现在，我们要... - 罗，快来！
- Now, here's what we're gonna do... - Ron, come quick!
她们发疯了，女孩们发疯了
They've gone wild. The girls have gone wild.
一片狼藉，氛围中充斥着文字抨击
It was full-tilt jungle madness.
不可避免了
And it wasn't going away.
嘿，我把这两个分开了
Hey, I pulled these two off each other.
卡尔教练，别靠近未成年女孩
Coach Carr, step away from the underage girls.
让我帮你下来
Let me help you down there.
该死，不！我不会让这样下去的！
Hell, no! I did not leave the Southside for this!
噢，讨厌！我的头发！
Oh, crap! My hair!
所有低年级女生立即到体育馆报到！立刻！
All junior girls report to the gymnasium immediately! Immediately!
你曾经向满是议论你的...
Have you ever walked up to people
人群走过去的经历吗？
and realized they were just talking about you?
你有连续60次走过吗？
Have you ever had it happen 60 times in a row?
我有
I have.
在我14年的教学生涯中 从来没遇到过这种行为
Never in my 1 4 years as an educator have I seen such behavior.
而且还都是女孩
And from young ladies.
我接到你们父母的电话，“有没有人受伤？”
I got parents calling me on the phone asking, "Did someone get shot?"
我应该取消你们的春季狂欢会
I ought to cancel your Spring Fling.
不！
No!
- 不 - 我们怎么办？
- No. - What are we supposed to do?
现在，我不会那样做 我们已经给主持人付了钱
Now, I'm not gonna do that, because we've already paid the DJ.
但不要以为我对这本册子不重视
But don't think that I'm not taking this book seriously.
卡尔教练已经逃离了学校
Coach Carr has fled school property.
诺布里小姐已被指控贩毒
Ms. Norbury has been accused of selling drugs.
现在，你们这年级的女孩所需要的
Now, what the young ladies in this grade need
是态度的转变
is an attitude makeover.
你们不久就会实现这种转变
And you're gonna get it right now.
不管需要多少时间，我要你们今晚都呆在这
I don't care how long it takes, I will keep you here all night.
我们不能留过四点
We can't keep them past 4.
我要把你们留到四点
I will keep you here until 4.
现在，我要做的就是
Now, what we're gonna try to do is fix the way you young ladies
改变你们彼此间的关系
relate to each other.
好吗？女孩和女孩之间的关系
OK? Lady to lady.
有关女孩的问题，谁来讨论一下？
So who has a lady problem that they'd like to talk about?
请讲？
Yes?
书里写到，我说自己是处女是在撒谎
Somebody wrote in that book that I'm lying about being a virgin
因为我用超大号的卫生棉条
because I use super-jumbo tampons.
因为我的阴道太大 当我量大的时候只能那样
But I can't help it if I've got a heavy flow and a wide-set vagina.
是的，我无能为力
Yeah, I can't do this.
诺布里小姐
Ms. Norbury.
你是位成功的、睿智的、有同情心的女士
You're a successful, intelligent, caring, graceful woman.
我？
I am?
你肯定有些话想对这些年轻的女孩说
There has to be something you can say to these young ladies.
帮助她们改掉自大的毛病
Something to help them with their self-esteem?
这不是自大的问题
It's not a self-esteem problem.
我想她们对自己都很满意
I think they're all pretty pleased with themselves.
好
OK.
好，请所有人把眼睛闭上
OK. Everybody close your eyes.
认为被人背后说过坏话的
I want you to raise your hand if you have ever had a girl
请举手
say something bad about you behind your back.
睁开眼睛
Open your eyes.
下面，再闭上眼睛
Now, close your eyes again.
这次，在背后议论朋友的人
And this time, I want you to raise your hand if you have ever
请举手
said anything about a friend behind her back.
睁开眼睛
Open them.
这里有些女孩和女孩之间的矛盾
There's been some girl-on-girl crime here.
好，所以，今天我们来作些练习
OK. So, what we could do today is a couple exercises to help you
帮助你们用健康的方法表达愤怒
express your anger in a healthy way.
我们从这里开始
Let's start over here.
诺布里小姐让我们彼此直接面对
Ms. Norbury had us confront each other directly
这些困扰我们的事情
about the things that were bothering us.
似乎每个小圈子都有自己的问题
And it seemed like every clique had its own problems.
自从你成了一垒手就趾高气昂
You've been acting really stuck-up ever since you switched to shortfielder.
道恩也同意我的意见
And Dawn agrees with me.
- 道恩？ - 不要把我扯进去
- Dawn? - Don't drag me into this,
明天我还要投球
I'm pitching tomorrow.
为什么你要骗走我的男朋友？
是你嫉妒男生更喜欢我一些
尼加，拜托
好，很好
OK. Good.
我可以说在这所学校里 我们没有任何圈子问题吗？
Can I just say that we don't have a clique problem at this school?
我们之中，有些人根本不必作这个练习
And some of us shouldn't have to take this workshop, because some of us
因为我们只是受害者
are just victims in this situation.
这可能是事实，有多少人
That's probably true. How many of you
认为你们曾被莉贾娜・乔治欺负过？
have ever felt personally victimized by Regina George?
很好，好了，谁是下一个？
Good. OK, who's next?
谁是下一个？
Who's next?
凯蒂
Cady.
你有没有什么想坦白的？
Do you have anything you wanna own up to?
有...不
Yes. No.
你从未散播过别人的谣言？
You never made up a rumor about anybody?
就像说你贩毒的事
Just that you sell drugs.
没有
No.
没有你想道歉的？
Nothing you want to apologize for?
我不能向诺布里女士道歉
I couldn't apologize to Ms. Norbury
要是整本《红唇烈焰之书》没有我的责任
without getting blamed for the whole Burn Book.
不
No.
我对你太失望了，凯蒂
I'm really disappointed in you, Cady.
好，我们来这是为了这本书，对吗？
OK, so we're all here because of this book, right?
呃...我不知道，谁写了这本书
Well, I don't know who wrote this book,
但是你们必须立刻停止互相骂荡妇和妓女
but you all have got to stop calling each other sluts and whores.
男孩子骂你们荡妇和妓女还行
It just makes it OK for guys to call you sluts and whores.
这里谁被骂过荡妇？
Who here has ever been called a slut?
好，大家起立
OK, everybody up.
诺布里小姐叫我们向
Ms. Norbury had us write out apologies
受过我们伤害的人道歉
to people that we'd hurt in our lives.
“阿莉萨，抱歉我叫过你暴牙婊子
"Alyssa, I'm sorry I called you a gap-toothed bitch.
“你暴牙，这不是你的错”
"It's not your fault you're so gap-toothed."
"格雷琴，
"Gretchen,
“我很抱歉上次在邦诺书店
"I'm sorry I laughed at you that time you got diarrhea
“你腹泻的时候嘲笑你
"at Barnes and Noble.
“另外我非常抱歉告诉所有人”
"And I'm sorry I told everyone about it."
抱歉我现在又说了一遍
And I'm sorry for repeating it now.
劳拉，我不是因为你胖而恨你
Laura, I don't hate you because you're fat.
因为我恨你，所以说你胖
You're fat because I hate you.
我只希望我们能象中学时一样要好
I just wish we could all get along like we used to in middle school.
我希望我能烤一个彩虹和微笑做成的蛋糕
I wish that I could bake a cake made out of rainbows and smiles,
我们一起享用，分享快乐
and we'd all eat it and be happy.
她不是这儿的
She doesn't even go here!
你是我们学校的吗？
Do you even go to this school?
不，我只是有很多感触
No. I just have a lot of feelings.
好啦，回家去吧
OK, go home.
莎伦，我认为你做得很好
Sharon, I think you're doing a great job.
谢谢，我想我会把事情解决的
Thanks. I feel like I'm getting through.
很遗憾，这么多人嫉妒我
I'm sorry that people are so jealous of me.
但是受欢迎不是我的错
But I can't help it that I'm popular.
哦，上帝！噢，呀 好了，走开，走开
Oh, my God! Oh, jeez. OK, walk it off. Walk it off.
没事，真疼啊
OK. That hurt.
她们没事
They're OK.
噢，男孩们，好了，谁下一个？ 谁下一个？继续
Oh, boy. OK, who's next? Who's next? Keep it going.
噢，上帝，她要梦想成真了 跳进一群女人当中
Oh, my God. It's her dream come true, diving into a big pile of girls.
噢，是的，我要道个歉
OK, yeah, I've got an apology.
我有一个朋友，今年的新生
So I have this friend who is a new student this year.
我说服她扰乱莉贾娜・乔治的生活 这是很有趣的事
And I convinced her that it would be fun to mess up Regina George's life.
所以我让她假装和莉贾娜交朋友
So I had her pretend to be friends with Regina,
这样她就可以来到我家
and then she would come to my house after
而我们就可以嘲笑莉贾娜所说的傻话
and we would just laugh about all the dumb stuff Regina said.
我们还给她吃糖果棒
And we gave her these candy bar things
让她增肥了
that would make her gain weight,
我们还离间她最好的朋友
and we turned her best friends against her.
还有...噢，是的，凯蒂... 我的朋友凯蒂
And then... Oh, yeah, Cady... You know my friend Cady.
和莉贾娜的男朋友有一腿
She made out with Regina's boyfriend
叫他和莉贾娜分手
and then convinced him to break up with her.
噢，上帝，她给你的是 搽脚油，而不是洁面乳
Oh, God, and we gave you foot cream instead of face wash.
上帝！很抱歉，莉贾娜
God! I am so sorry, Regina.
真的，我不知道自己在作什么
Really, I don't know why I did it.
我想这可能是因为 我爱上你了
I guess it's probably because I've got a big lesbian crush on you.
真恶心！
Suck on that!
珍尼斯！珍尼斯！珍尼斯！珍尼斯！
Janis! Janis! Janis! Janis!
莉贾娜！
Regina!
莉贾娜，等等！我不想这样的
Regina, wait! I didn't mean for that to happen.
每个人都恨我？没关系
To find out that everyone hates me? I don't care.
莉贾娜，拜托！莉贾娜，别！
Regina, please! Regina, stop!
不！你知道别人是怎么说你的吗？
No! Do you know what everyone says about you?
她们说你是接受家庭式教育的怪物
They say that you're a home-schooled jungle freak,
是我的另一个不太性感的翻版
who's a less-hot version of me.
是的, 别再表现的那么天真了
Yeah. So don't try to act so innocent.
你可以接受那个虚假的道歉 然后将其置之脑后...
You can take that fake apology and shove it right up your hairy...
莉贾娜・乔治就那样死了
And that's how Regina George died.
不，只是个玩笑，但她的确受伤了
No, I'm totally kidding. But she did get hurt.
有人看见她的头到处滚
Some girls say they saw her head go all the way around.
但那只是谣言，有人发誓说看见我
But that's just a rumor. Some people swear they saw me
把她推到车前，这是更糟糕的谣言
push her in front of the bus. That was an even worse rumor.
- 都吃完了吗? - 没，妈妈，那不是我写的
- Everybody done? - No. Mom, I didn't do it.
我不知道应该相信什么
I don't know what to believe anymore.
妈妈，相信我，我是你女儿
Mom, believe me. I'm your daughter.
为什么我部落的花瓶在水池底下？
Why are my tribal vases under the sink?
我的花瓶！为什么在下面？
My tribal vases. Why were they under the sink?
我不知道
I don't know.
这是象征丰收的，尼贝利部落的花瓶
This is the fertility vase of the Ndebele tribe.
- 对你有意义吗? - 没有
- Does that mean anything to you? - No.
你到底是谁？
Who are you?
绝好，所有的朋友恨我 现在连我的妈妈也恨我
Great. All my friends hate me, and now my mom hates me.
你母亲不是恨你
Your mom does not hate you.
她是担心你
She's afraid of you.
我不知道，也许是我们急于让你接受主流教育
I don't know, maybe we mainstream-schooled you too soon.
也许你应该再接受一段时间的家庭式教育
Maybe you should come back and be home-schooled again for a while.
不，再调换回来会变得更糟糕
No. Only thing worse than going back will be not going back.
明天会更糟糕吗？
How bad's it gonna be tomorrow?
记得我们看到那些狮子 同野猪打仗的场景吗？
Remember when we saw those lions fighting over the wart hog carcass?
我就是那野猪
I'll be the wart hog.
你不是野猪
You're not a wart hog,
你是头狮子
you're a lion.
集中精力学习一段时间
Just focus on your studies for a little while.
你还是个优秀的学生，对吗？
You're still an excellent student, right?
哦，对，我需要你在我的微积分试卷上签字
Oh, yeah. I need you to sign my calculus test.
- 为什么？ - 我没及格
- Why? - I'm failing.
好，你...
OK. You are...
这叫作什么？
What do they call it?
被挂了
Grounded.
你被挂了
You're grounded.
她把她推到车前
She pushed her in front of the bus.
你看到她推了吗？
Did you see her do it?
是的
Yes.
你们的老师有没有卖大麻或摇头丸给你们？
Did your teacher ever try to sell you marijuana or Ecstasy tablets?
- 没有 - 什么是摇头丸？
- No. - What are marijuana tablets?
发生什么事？诺布里小姐在哪?
What's going on? Where's Ms. Norbury?
杜瓦尔先生，太可笑了，诺布里小姐没有贩毒
Mr. Duvall, this is ridiculous. Ms. Norbury does not sell drugs.
我知道，亚伦，但是自从对卡尔教练的猜测
I know, Aaron. But after the allegations against Coach Carr
变得完全真实可信之后
turned out to be extremely true,
学校董事会认为还是应该调查
the school board felt that it was best that we investigate every claim made
一下《红唇烈火之书》里所说的每件事
in this Burn Book.
那本书是由一帮笨女孩写的
That book was written by a bunch of stupid girls
她们制造谣言是由于
who make up rumors because they're bored
她们厌烦了无聊的生活
with their own lame lives.
呃...除非谁站出来说，“都是我写的”
Well, unless someone wants to come forward and say, "l made it all up",
否则我们只有这样处理，说有人...
this is how we have to handle it. To say that someone...
噢，不，再见，亚伦，你会永远恨我
Oh, no. Bye, Aaron. You're gonna hate me forever.
杜瓦尔先生
Mr. Duvall.
是我写的
I wrote it.
来，凯蒂
Come on, Cady.
当你被蛇咬了一口
When you get bit by a snake,
你就要把毒液吸出来
you're supposed to suck the poison out.
那就是我要做的 把我生活中的毒液全吸出来
That's what I had to do. Suck all the poison out of my life.
从莉贾娜开始
I started with Regina,
她是活生生的证明 怕你的人越多
who was living proof that the more people are scared of you,
得到的花就越多
the more flowers you get.
接下来是诺布里小姐
Then there was Ms. Norbury,
她也是活生生的证明 不做坏事不会受惩罚
who was living proof that no good deed goes unpunished.
噢，嗨，想买毒品吗？
Oh, hi. Did you wanna buy some drugs?
- 我只是做完了试卷 - 等会，我现在就评分
- I'm just done with my quiz. - Wait. I'll grade it right now.
我得说，看着警察搜查我的房间
I gotta say, watching the police search my house
真是这不可思议的一年中 最值得记忆的事情
really was the cherry on top of a fantastic year.
把事实说出来很困难吧？
How much trouble did you get in for telling the truth?
很难
A lot.
整本书不全是你写的
You didn't write that whole book yourself.
有没有告诉杜瓦尔先生还有谁？
Did you tell Mr. Duvall who else did it?
没有，因为我想尝试一下新方法
No, because I'm trying this new thing
不在别人背后议论
where I don't talk about people behind their backs.
没错，被车撞一下的确是个很好的教训
That's all right. Getting hit by a bus is pretty good punishment.
94分
Ninety-four.
欢迎回来，讨厌的家伙
Welcome back, nerd.
多谢
Thanks.
怎么说...
Anyway...
...我非常抱歉
...I'm sorry.
我原谅你
I forgive you.
但是作为我给你的惩罚
But as my own personal form of punishment,
我告诉你如何得到额外的学分
I figured out how you're gonna earn that extra credit.
该怎么办？
What's up?
太棒了，今年出席的人很多
Excellent. Great turnout this year.
- 好，就看你们的了 - 好
- All right. It's all you. - OK.
- 让我们打败他们 - 好
- Make me look good out there. - OK.
玛丽蒙，你们这群婊子养的 你们连婊子养的都不如
Marymount, you sons of bitches. You no-good sons of bitches.
- 你紧张吗？ - 是
- You nervous? - Yes.
不要紧张，你行的 没有什么能影响你的注意力
Don't be. You can do this. There's nothing to break your focus,
因为玛丽蒙的男孩没一个帅的
because not one of those Marymount boys is cute.
晚安，先生们女士们
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
欢迎参加伊利诺斯州州高中数学竞赛
Welcome to the lllinois High School Mathletes State Championship.
现在开始，第一个问题
Let's start the competition. Here is the first question.
有两个数，数值大的两倍加三是
Twice the larger of two numbers is three more than five times
数值小的五倍，数值大的四倍与
the smaller, and the sum of four times the larger
数值小的三倍之和是71 请问这两位数是...？
and three times the smaller is 71. What are...?
- 北岸高中？ - 14和5
- North Shore? - Fourteen and five.
正确 第二个问题
That is correct. Question number two.
找一个三位数的奇数，各位数之和是12
Find an odd three-digit number whose digits add up to 1 2.
三位数都不相同，前两位数的差值
The digits are all different, and the difference between the first two digits
和后两位数的差值相等
equals the difference between...
- 玛丽蒙？ - 741
- Marymount? - 741.
- 正确 - 浪费，我真迟钝
- Correct. - Shoot. I was really rusty.
- 凯蒂在哪？ - 她出去了
- Where's Cady? - She went out.
她都被挂了
She's grounded.
被挂了就不能出去吗？
Are they not allowed out when they're grounded?
大家别忘了为选春季狂欢会国王和王后投票
Don't forget to vote for Spring Fling King and Queen, people.
选中的人会在一年内代表你们
These A-holes will represent you for a full calendar year.
我选莉贾娜・乔治，因为她被车撞了
I'm gonna vote for Regina George because she got hit by that bus.
我选凯蒂・海伦，因为她推了她
I'm voting for Cady Heron because she pushed her.
她都被挂了，但他还让她出去
She's supposed to be grounded, but he let her out.
经过87分钟激烈的比赛，我们得到平局
After 87 minutes of very competitive play, we have a tie.
在打平的情况下，我们进入突然死亡回合
In the event of a tie, we move into a sudden-death round.
两队均可选择他们的对手
Each team is given the opportunity to choose their opponent.
- 北岸高中，你们选谁？ - 那个女孩，哥们，选那个女孩
- North Shore, who do you select? - The girl, dude. The girl.
克拉夫特选手
Contestant Krafft.
来自玛丽蒙队的卡洛琳・卡拉夫特小姐
From Marymount, Miss Caroline Krafft.
我们也选女的
We pick the girl too.
来自北岸高中的堪蒂・海伦小姐
And from North Shore, Miss Cady Heron.
是凯蒂
It's Cady.
噢，上帝，是我
Oh, my God, that's me.
卡洛琳・克拉夫特小姐急需修眉
Miss Caroline Krafft seriously needed to pluck her eyebrows.
她的样子看上去好像是 星期日盲文班的老师挑出来的
Her outfit looked like it was picked out by a blind Sunday school teacher.
把99％的唇膏涂在她的暴牙上
And she had some 99-cent lip gloss on her snaggletooth.
就在那时我意识到 取笑卡洛琳・克拉夫特
And that's when I realized, making fun of Caroline Krafft
不能阻止她在竞赛中打败我
wouldn't stop her from beating me in this contest.
选手们，给出这个式子的极限值
Contestants, find the limit of this equation.
说别人胖，不可能使自己变瘦
Calling somebody else fat won't make you any skinnier.
叫别人傻瓜，自己不会变聪明
Calling someone stupid doesn't make you any smarter.
而毁了莉贾娜・乔治一生 也一定不会让我更加快乐
And ruining Regina George's life definitely didn't make me any happier.
生活中要做的就是 努力解决在你面前的问题
All you can do in life is try to solve the problem in front of you.
- 极限值是负一 - 哦，糟糕，我输了
- The limit is negative one. - Oh, crap. I lost.
答案不正确
That answer is incorrect.
现在我们采用的是突然死亡法 如果海伦小姐能够正确回答
Now, we are in a sudden death. If Miss Heron can answer
...这个问题，冠军就产生了
this problem correctly, we have a winner.
极限值，为什么我一点也想不起极限的东西？
Limits. Why couldn't I remember anything about limits?
极限值，那个礼拜亚伦剪了头发
Limits. That was the week Aaron got his hair cut.
噢，上帝，他瞧上去真可爱 好，集中注意力，凯蒂
Oh, God, he looked so cute. OK, focus, Cady.
亚伦脑后的黑板上写着什么来着？
What was on the board behind Aaron's head?
如果极限不接近任何...
If the limit never approaches anything...
极限就不存在
The limit does not exist.
这个极限不存在！
The limit does not exist!
我们的新冠军
Our new state champions,
- 是北岸高中数奥队 - 太棒了！
- the North Shore Mathletes. - Yeah!
喜欢我吗？
How do you like me now?
喜欢吗？耶！来点！来点啊！
You like that? Yeah! Get some! Get some!
太棒了，穿上这皮袖子
Awesome. You went with the leather sleeves.
- 非洲人，你太厉害了 - 多谢
- Africa, you did the damn thing. - Thanks.
谢了，凯文・纳泊尔
Thanks, K.G.
我们穿着这个去“春季狂欢节”舞会 大家会吃惊死的
We're gonna look so kick-ass in these when we roll into Spring Fling.
- 噢，不，我不去了 - 什么？
- Oh, no, I'm not going. - What?
凯蒂，这是属于你的夜晚，不要让恨你的人
Cady, this is your night. Don't let the haters
阻止你做你自己的“事体”
stop you from doing your thang.
你刚才说“事体”？
Did you just say "thang"?
凯蒂，你不必永远自责
Cady, you don't have to punish yourself forever.
但是我被挂了
But I'm grounded.
你已经走出了那个胡同
You're already out.
好，所有国王和王后的候选人
All right, do we have all of our nominees
在台上了吗？
for king and queen on the stage?
好，很好，我只是想说你们都是胜利者
OK, good. I just wanted to say that you're all winners.
我很高兴，这个学年即将结束
And I could not be happier that this school year's ending.
现在，春季狂欢节国王是...
Here we go. The winner of the Spring Fling King,
- 谢恩・阿曼 - 耶！
- Shane Oman. - Yes!
我说吧！
That's what I'm talking about!
王后是...
And your Spring Fling Queen,
学生会下任副主席
future co-chair of the Student Activities Board
并赢得沃克兄弟薄烤饼屋
and winner of two gift certificates
的两张优惠券资格
to the Walker Brothers Pancake House,
凯蒂・海伦
Cady Heron.
凯蒂在哪？
Where is Cady?
她在那儿
There she is.
谢谢
Thanks.
呃，房间里半数人讨厌我
Well, half the people in this room are mad at me.
另外一半喜欢我
And the other half only like me
是因为她们以为我把某人推到车前
because they think I pushed somebody in front of a bus.
所以这不太好
So that's not good.
你知道，并不是真要你发表演讲
You know, it's not really required of you to make a speech.
就快说完了，我保证
I'm almost done, I swear.
对《烈焰红唇之书》里受到伤害的所有人
To all the people whose feelings that got hurt by the Burn Book,
我真的非常抱歉
I'm really sorry.
你们知道，这些事我以前从来没经历过
You know, I've never been to one of these things before.
当我想到有多少人想要这个
And when I think about how many people wanted this
有多少人为此流泪...
and how many people cried over it and stuff...
我想说，今晚每个人看上去都是青春王族
I mean, I think everybody looks like royalty tonight.
瞧杰希卡・洛佩兹，她的衣服真漂亮
Look at Jessica Lopez. That dress is amazing.
还有埃玛・格贝，我想说， 这个发型肯定花了好几个小时
And Emma Gerber, I mean, that hairdo must have taken hours,
你看起来也很漂亮
and you look really pretty.
所以...
So...
...为什么每个人要为此而紧张呢？
...why is everybody stressing over this thing?
我想说，这只是块塑料，只能...
I mean, it's just plastic. Could really just...
大家分享吧
Share it.
一片给格雷琴・维纳斯 她也是“春季狂欢节王后”
A piece for Gretchen Wieners, a partial Spring Fling Queen.
一片给珍尼斯・伊安
A piece for Janis lan.
真的，大多数人拿了皇冠就走了
Seriously, most people just take the crown and go.
还有一片给莉贾娜・乔治
And a piece for Regina George.
她的脊骨骨折了 但是看上去仍然象一位摇滚明星
She fractured her spine, and she still looks like a rock star.
谢谢
Thank you.
其它的给在座所有的
And some for everybody else.
上帝，杜瓦尔先生，你来结束语好吗？
God, Mr. Duvall, can you wrap it up?
谢谢
Thanks.
好，各位，玩得开心
All right, have a good time, everyone.
瞧，我是王后
Look. I'm a queen.
我也是
As am l.
- 嘿 - 嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
我们还继续吵架吗？
So are we still in a fight?
你还是混蛋吗？
Are you still an asshole?
我想不是了
I don't think so.
行，我想我们和好了
Well, then I guess we're OK.
哦，上帝，我喜欢这首歌
Oh, my God, I love this song!
我讨厌这首歌
I hate this song.
我知道这首歌！
I know this song!
主角上场了
Man candy, stage right.
- 嘿，怎么样？ - 嘿，没想到你赢了
- Hey, what's up? - Hey. Didn't think you'd make it.
代表高年级，我想送你两张礼券...
On behalf of the senior class, I'd like to present you with two gift certificates...
- 谢谢，烂人 - 哦，好静
- Thanks, sucker. - Yo, peace.
一张沃克兄弟薄烤饼屋的礼券
One gift certificate to the Walker Brothers Pancake House.
谢谢
Thank you.
祝贺你赢得比赛
Congratulations on winning State.
我当时很紧张，做极限的题目
I was so nervous. They made us do limits.
我想我快输了
I thought I was gonna hurl.
- 你的胃现在怎么样？ - 没问题
- How's your stomach now? - It's fine.
- 想吐吗？ - 不
- Do you feel nauseous at all? - No.
- 你喝酒了吗？ - 没有
- Have you been drinking? - No.
好
OK.
“棒酷”
Grool.
不
No.
- 怎么了？ - 我能帮你吗？
- What's up? - Can I help you?
你是波多黎各人？
You Puerto Rican?
黎巴嫩人
Lebanese.
感觉到了
I feel that.
毋庸置疑，“魔鬼身材”解散了
In case you're wondering, The Plastics broke up.
莉贾娜的脊骨愈合了，她的理疗医师
Regina's spine healed, and her physical therapist
引导她参加各类活动
taught her to channel all her rage into sports.
那儿很好，球场的姑娘都不怕她
It was perfect because the jock girls weren't afraid of her.
克伦用她的特殊能力去做了早晨天气预报员
Karen used her special talents to do the morning weather announcements.
嗨，我是克伦・史密斯，今天气温68度
Hi. This is Karen Smith. It's 68 degrees,
30％的降水概率
and there's a 30 percent chance that it's already raining.
格雷琴建了自己的小圈子
And Gretchen found herself a new clique
又有个新蜂后产生了
and a new queen bee to serve.
亚伦去了西北，我还是周末去看他
Aaron went to Northwestern, so I still get to see him on weekends.
我呢？
And me?
我从家庭式教育的怪物 变成了耀眼的“魔鬼身材”一员
I had gone from home-schooled jungle freak to shiny Plastic
又变成人人讨厌的人 最后变成了普通人
to most hated person in the world to actual human being.
嘿
Hey.
去年以来的所有故事都已经不重要了
All the drama from last year just wasn't important anymore.
学校曾经像个鲨鱼池，而今我已能够在里面戏水
School used to be like a shark tank, but now I could just float.
莉贾娜
Regina.
“女孩世界”最终还是平静了
Finally, Girl World was at peace.
嘿，瞧，低年级的“魔鬼身材”
Hey, check it out. Junior Plastics.
如果有新人企图破坏这一平静...
And if any freshmen tried to disturb that peace...
嗯，我们只能说，我们知道该怎么处理了
Well, let's just say we knew how to take care of it.
开个玩笑！
Just kidding.